Chino is going to tell you all about
that. So, please give a big round of
applause
for our host, our MC.
>> He's coming up slowly.
>> One step at a time for his own
sunglasses.
>> Right.
>> Here he comes.
>> Well, I got to set it up, too. So,
>> you got to set it up. Oh,
>> yeah. You were doing your thing before I
showed up.
>> Oh, okay.
He'll be here. He's here, but he'll be
check.
>> There he is.
>> He's checking.
>> Check. Check.
>> Check. Check. Check.
>> Cuz I can only hear this speaker right
here.
>> Yeah, it's just pointing pretty.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, warm
welcome for Gino Laforge, please. Thank
you.
>> Give it up for Dub, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> Thank you very much. By the way, one of
Contributions, there's a QR code to be
right here on his side.
>> Yes. Check out his QR code. What is your
uh Venmo again? Dove, if you want, Venmo
is
at Evan Dove. Evan N o and the number
three. That's Evan Dove three because
Evan Dove one and two are taken. Who are
these first two people? Double gangers.
One more time for Dub, ladies and
gentlemen. Keep it going, bro. Thank
you. We're going to let him break down.
We're going to get this mic set up.
We're going to get this show started in
no time. Uh, welcome to Bay Coffee and
Bar on a Monday night.
It's time for comedy. Who came here for
comedy tonight?
>> Who did not come here for comedy? and
comedy is just kind of happening to
them.
>> All right, good. That's a good ratio.
That means word's getting out. This is
Monday night comedy night. The comedy
simulator is called that because this is
not a real comedy show. This is a
simulated comedy experience. What does
that mean? You are not a real audience.
We are not real comedians. What does
that mean? Nobody's asking for your
money, so lower your expectations.
That's what this all means. This is all
us dressing up an open mic to look
better than it is. You're going to see a
lot of new comedy tonight, friends.
Cutting edge comedy, as I like to say.
And the thing about the cutting edge is
that sometimes it looks like bad comedy.
That's kind of a part of being on the
cutting edge. Uh, you're going to see
some moments of brilliance. You're going
to see some moments that aren't so
great. It's all a part of the show.
We're going to pretend like we're the
best comedians you've ever heard. You're
going to pretend like you're the best
audience we've ever had, and we're going
to fake it till we make it. That's how
this show works. Uh, thank you. Sillow
clap. Awkward in the back.
That's the type of clap that gets you
kicked off of jury duty, isn't it?
Right. You're not supposed to clap in
that situation. They don't want that.
Get out of here, buddy. Uh, so we have
themes every week. Last week was heckle
night. If some of you were here, you saw
how intense the show could be. Tonight's
a lot more laidback, friends. We're
doing duet night, duos, double sets, two
comedians for the price of one. We're
going to have two comics on stage.
They're going to be trying to work out a
set for you in front of you. And we're
going to have some moments of amazing
hilarity. And we're going to have some
moments where you're like, "What is
going on here? What are they saying? Why
are they still talking?" We're going to
get through it together. This is also
being live streamed. Give it up for
Skyler from Shroom Studios over here.
>> The gentleman in the hat that would have
given you newspaper in the 1930s. Uh he
is our video producer from Shroomcat and
my my buddy. Uh he is the one that makes
us look so incredible. The live stream
is @ comedy simulator on YouTube. Last
week we had 82,000 viewers on the show.
Um yeah, thank you. Thank you. Check it
out from your phones. Join the comment
section. They're very ruthlessly
horrible to us. And uh that's what gets
us 82,000 people watching is just
everybody dog piling on us. It's
hilarious. Join the madness. See how
mean people can be to us at comedy
simulator on YouTube. People streaming.
Uh follow, like, subscribe, chat. Do you
do all that stuff? Um let's see the
theme. Uh audience member of the night.
I normally gift you with hot sauce
because it's a working holiday. I did
not work today. So I will find a prize
for you. Audience member of the night.
What do you do to be audience member of
the night? You be a good audience
member. You stay for the entire show. If
I notice those two things, you could win
a prize. Uh comedian of the night last
week, Jimbo, congratulations. won a spot
on Jose's show at the playground.
Crushed. Ivan crushed. I heard the the
Maui Comics did their job. Good job,
boys. Appreciate you for doing the heavy
lifting. Good work. Um, all right. So,
we're doing double sets. I will start
with a comic and then I will start
bringing on the comedians. Comedians,
your sets have been extended. Since you
have two comics on a set, you can go up
to 10 minutes. Now, don't feel like you
have to do 10 minutes. If you can't do
10 minutes, we a minute of of hard
material is hard enough. We don't need 3
minutes of two people figuring it out,
right? That's kind of weird. That's like
watching an Only Fans of like a a one
night stand. Just the rhythm's all off.
It's not working. What's going on here?
We don't want Nobody wants to see that.
They don't want to see that. We don't
want to see that. So, if you guys are
feel like cutting this set short, go
ahead, ramp it up. We'll get you off the
stage. I'll be there to catch you. All
right. Are we ready to begin the comedy
simulator?
>> Are we ready for the simulation to
begin?
Let's begin simulation.
I'm going to bring up my comedy partner
for tonight. Let's go ahead and bring up
my buddy, recent adult parents, my
friend Bashar. Coming up on stage, bud
microphone. We have two mics here.
>> Okay. Thank you guys. Is this volume
okay, everybody? We didn't have a chance
to check it yet. Go ahead, check it.
>> I don't know about this uh Only Fans
[ __ ] you was talking about, but
we're here. We're here. Both of us. Can
you guys hear us?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> I don't know why you're not thinking
about Only Fans. You guys are You have
You're a good-looking couple. That's
something that that could be in the
future. I mean,
>> yeah.
>> I'm not I'm not saying you should. Just
you could.
>> Yeah. I was thinking about us, Gino.
>> Oh, you and me.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> I mean,
>> cuz we're on stage. This is what you
brought up.
>> You know the who's on first bit. It's
more like who's pitching, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Who's pitching is catching.
>> Okay. Who do you guys would be pitching,
guys? Who do you think be bitching?
>> Gino, give it up.
>> You think I'm top applaud right now if
you think I'm the top of this
relationship.
>> Okay. Apply right now if I'm the top.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Bob's over back. That's what
it looks like.
>> I'm I'm gay after all. Hey, you're
you're you're the top, which makes you
the less desirable.
>> Back home, it's not even gay. Actually,
that's just what you do.
>> Wait, there's no ladies around. So,
>> you know, there there's there's some
American military that would agree. Uh,
a deployment long enough, right, Mr. You
get it. Um,
>> so Bashar,
>> yeah,
>> you just recently became a dad,
>> man. Give it up, guys.
>> Congratulations. Yeah, for Bashar. I
have a
Yeah, I have a I have a 4 days old baby
right now. She's well taken care of.
Don't worry about that. She got her mom
and her grandma looking after her. You
know, that's the first question that
comes up. I'm start realizing it's a
one-sided relationship in this thing,
right? I'm doing all this [ __ ] A baby
is not pitching with nothing. So, I went
ahead and used her social security for a
couple of credit cards just in case. Oh,
you did what my parents did.
That's why I got I had to go for
scholarships. Uh so, um are you going to
do what most Middle Eastern fathers do
and spoil the crap out of your daughter
to the point where she'll never get
married because no man can live up to
that?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, we're not in the
Middle East. The thing I'm worried about
is, you know, we're going to grow in a
time where she's going to grow up in a
time where robots and AI might be
already being partners, right? And I
don't know how to answer. Like if she
bring me a robot that identifies as a
Muslim,
>> that's right. You're you're going to be
a part of the first wave of parents that
have to be like, "Dad, you know,
>> this robot's my boyfriend."
>> Okay. Like, blow yourself up. Let me
know you're real.
>> Okay.
>> What do you believe in, robot?
>> Oh, man. Yeah. No, that that's going to
be weird. Who knows what robots are
going to be uh taking over for by the
time
>> you're I mean they might be doing stand
up comedy for us be doing
>> Yeah.
>> Do you think a duo set between two
robots would be like having Alexa talk
with Alexa
>> where it's like order me a pizza? It's
like I would like to do that. How can I
help you? It's like hello, I'm here to
help. And they just keep going back and
forth.
>> Yes. Yes. I think I think that'd be very
close to what's going on. You guys heard
the uh Chinese restaurants prank where
two Chinese restaurants talk to each
other. Feel like it'll be the same
thing. I love Chinese people by the way,
but there's gone around. So I'm just
picking on on the nonavailables right
now, which is Indians, Chinese. I don't
know what you are, bro. I'm just It's
okay. You're you're technically Asian,
right? The Middle East is in Asia.
>> Yes.
>> I I was having this conversation
recently. Uh, an Indian friend of mine
was like, "No, we're Asian, too." And I
was like, "Get the [ __ ] out of here. No
way. I never thought of it like that,
right? We don't when you think of
Asians, you don't think of Indians." But
then he was like, "No, we're Asians,
too. We identify as Asians." And I think
that if you identify as Asians, you have
to let other Asians do your accent.
That's the only thing that makes it
legit, right? Is that like I'm Korean,
I'm allowed to do Japanese, Filipino,
like I'm allowed to. But Indian has
always been controversial. So Indians,
if you want to be Asian, you have to let
us
>> do the accent.
>> Do your accents?
>> Yes. Yes. You got to let us do the
accent.
>> I don't see one to verify. So I'm not
going to do the accents.
>> Are there any Indians? No. Go ahead,
Gino.
>> That's how you get cancelled. Um. Yeah.
>> So how how's uh how's you? So Bashar
rents mopeds uh for his business. How's
the tourism industry been? How's the
mopeds been?
>> It's good. It's good. I'm renting a lot
of mopeds. I missed few calls today
because I had a baby. Um, so I might be
losing some business. Yeah, if you guys
want to rent some mopeds, I'm in Kihei,
uh, Maui Scooter Company. Come get some
mopeds.
Um, and there's no joke in there, you
know, but things are tough.
>> It's the first Muslimowned LGBT scooter
renting shop. And this is I wish this
was a joke, but uh my mother-in-law is
actually gay and I haven't told my
family yet. So, Oo,
>> is that going to is that going to be a
dinner or a Zoom call? I feel like
that's a Zoom call.
>> Okay, this is this is a true story. My
my brother surprised me yesterday and he
flew from from um California. He lives
in California and came to visit us and
that was the first time he meets the
mother-in-law. And I'm like, just
please, you know, just get along for,
you know, my brother is super Muslim.
You know, I I kind of try to say I'm a
Muslim, but you'll catch me drinking and
smoking. My brother is super Muslim and
and my uh mother-in-law like short hair,
the whole deal. But they got along. They
got along. I wish there was a joke
there.
>> Super Muslim. That sounds like a
superhero.
>> Yes. I think I think I think we're at a
time where uh we can have a Muslim
superhero. Do you guys agree?
>> You can clap to that.
>> Hey, why not? Why not? Right. Right.
Dream big.
>> What? Hold on. First of all, Muslim
superhero. Would it be Marvel or DC?
>> DC.
>> DC. A little bit darker, a little bit
grittier. Okay, that's that's that's
that.
>> I I'll take it.
>> Little more dramatic.
>> Would it Would it Would it be a man or a
woman?
>> Black Adam. Black. Black. Oh,
>> a woman, right? Okay, that's a good
answer because a woman will have a mask
already, right?
>> Okay.
>> She's already ready to fight crime. Who
is that? I don't know.
>> Yeah. Her her superpower would be would
be shooting lasers lasers at any food
and making it halal food. So, that's uh
>> that would be the only superhero whose
alter ego and superhero is the same
vestage because you just can't identify
them either way. They're like
Yeah, I think the only thing that would
suck is she'll be able to fly but can't
drive. She's she's from Saudi Arabia.
That's that's the
>> Okay, where are we going with this?
>> That's why that's why you came to
America to open a scooter shop that's
>> I I like that he says that it's LGBT
friendly because you can't rent scooters
and not be like a little gay, right?
Let's be honest.
>> Yeah.
>> Especially if you're coming with two
people on one scooter. That's like
there's no straight way for two guys to
ride a sc a scooter
>> unless it's on the shoulders, right?
>> Cuz that's not gay. That's [ __ ]
awesome.
>> To a wheelie.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. What else we talking about? You
know, how's things been with you?
>> Good. Good. I've uh I'm finishing up
this diet I'm doing. I've lost 60 lbs.
>> Give it up, guys. 60 lb year and a half.
Thank you. Thank you. Half half a
Backstreet Boy if you're counting. Um
yeah, it's uh I didn't do the drugs
either. I didn't do the shots or the the
tests or nothing. Uh I just starved
myself.
>> Yeah, apparently anorexia is only
anorexia if you're already thin.
>> Yeah, he he got he got bullied into it.
>> If you're fat and anorexic, you're just
on a diet. I just I didn't know that
until I started trying to talk to people
about it.
>> I talked to other guys about the diet.
They're like, "Man, that sounds rough.
You're only eating like 1,600 calories a
day? That's crazy for your size?" I
talked to a girl, they're like, "600
calories? You [ __ ] cow? Are you
kidding me? How are you going to fit
into that prom dress, you fat bitch?"
I'm like, "Oh my god." I I didn't know I
was scratching at previous traumas.
>> Yeah. We We call this Ramadan. We do
this every [ __ ] year.
We starve ourselves just, you know, for
the one and only the Lord. You guys
don't know nothing about that.
>> See, nothing. This is why you can't talk
about a diet with somebody from a third
world country. They're like, "Diet?
>> You mean daily life? You mean when we're
waiting for UNICEF, [ __ ] Like that
doesn't?"
>> Yes. When we were lifting weights, I
felt like he liked watching me suffer.
He was just like, "Good, you [ __ ] fat
white American pig. I hope it hurts."
Yeah. That's a reality. My girl is is
white. My girl is white. And and I have
this issue where I I can tolerate a lot
more than she does. And it's not for the
fact that I'm just tough. It just we
were under sanctions for so long that,
you know, meat wasn't around. There was
nothing around, you know. So, I just uh
don't complain as much. But I'm
learning. Um I'm looking at my baby and
trying to see what what am I going to
instill? What kind of what kind of um
disciplines, right? I think I'm going to
have to teach her how how to
intermittent fast pretty quick with the
with the way the economy is going. One
tit only. Okay. You don't get two tits.
Okay. If Trump don't open the straight
of her moose, I'mma have a low fat baby.
It's what's going to It's what's going
to happen.
>> A tariff baby.
>> And to be honest, like I don't care at
this point.
>> Just bomb them, you know? Bomb somebody.
[ __ ] open the thing. Lower the the
gas. I I flew the [ __ ] war over here.
Give me some cheap gas. Okay. Bomb
somebody.
That's That's Bashar's running slogan.
2026 Bashar for president. Bomb
somebody.
>> All right, that's our double set. Give
it up for Bashar, ladies and gentlemen.
>> Give it up for Chino, guys. Thank you
very much.
>> All right, so we're having more double
sets starting right now. Um, I believe
the first two people on the list are uh
an odd couple of sorts. The first one
runs the open mic on Tuesdays in Kihei.
Uh, the second one is Jimbo's landlord
slashroommate slash slashback and slash.
They do a lot of things. They go on
trips together. I've never hung out with
my landlord as much as as Jimbo hangs
out with his. I wonder I I hope he's
getting prorated. That's I hope there's
something there. Ladies and gentlemen,
GET IT FOR MORGAN AND JIMBO.
>> JAMIE. OH,
>> SORRY. Morgan and Jamie. Morgan and
Jamie. Sorry. [ __ ] off, Jimbo.
Jimbo, good to see you. You [ __ ] grew
and worked out. What? What the hell
happened? You're wearing glasses now,
too. Oh, no. There's Jimbo over there.
It's okay.
>> No, Jimbo is my slave name.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, one of my favorite
people in PA, Jamie.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah, man. No, I've been cruising. A lot
of work, a lot of a lot of blood, sweat,
and tears. Uh, the
>> [ __ ] are you bleeding over?
>> Yeah. Yeah, there's a lot of [ __ ] going
on, man. I been trying to pass this drug
test. I I bought seven bottles of fake
piss.
>> What? Okay.
>> That's right. I drank seven bottles of
fake piss.
>> You don't drink it. You just use it,
bro.
>> Wait.
>> I still failed the test.
>> What's your job? I've always wondered.
>> I'm on real piss now, though.
>> No. What? All right.
>> It tastes better.
>> Okay. What What do you do for work,
Morgan? I'm curious.
>> I'm a handyman.
>> Oh, stay away from me.
>> Jack of all trades.
>> Hand jobs. blow jobs, you know, all that
kind of handy stuff. Oh my god. You
know,
>> under the table work, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Stay away.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> No. What do you think I'm talking about?
>> I looked I looked up opaque in the
dictionary.
>> Well, I am technically a landlord for
now until the IRS shuts me down.
>> But, um, you know, I do need a handyman.
So, if you can you will have to pass a
drug test to work at my house, too. But,
>> I I promise I'm lenient. You can do acid
shrooms.
>> They say cops should pass a drug test.
>> No,
>> I disagree. I I think they should have
to be high.
>> No, I think you should inject them with
DMT.
>> Could you imagine if a cop was high like
automatically he had to be high like
freeze, don't move. I dropped my gun.
>> Actually, no. I changed my mind. I think
every cop should smoke salvia.
>> Salvia.
>> Yeah. And go through like six months.
>> Is that like a [ __ ] door or
something?
>> Salvia Blanca. Salvia Blancco. No. No.
Miley Cyrus smoked it though.
>> Ah,
>> Miley Cyrus.
>> Yeah.
>> Now she's something else.
>> No, she's not.
>> I I Yeah. I I don't know much about her.
>> Did you date her, too?
>> No.
>> No. Okay.
>> No. No. Thank you.
>> I heard she's hot.
>> I like my dog.
>> So, okay. Go ahead. I think you have a
question.
>> I I think my dog might have given me
fleas.
>> Dog. What the hell? You get uku and I
didn't know it was a sexually
transmitted disease.
>> Okay. Does anyone have a pencil? You can
check his head right now.
>> I did go to Summer Pal. I can I can
confirm.
>> Oh man.
>> You know how you tell a pickle is a
pickle?
>> Um, no.
>> If you drop it on the ground and it
bounces,
>> okay,
>> it's a pickle.
>> Okay.
>> If it doesn't bounce, it's not a pickle.
>> What if it floats?
>> My son.
>> Okay, we're going.
>> Also not a pickle.
>> All right, we keep going.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, so pickles, do they float? I said
instead of jumping over
>> if they float,
>> they're a pickle.
>> Okay. [ __ ]
>> Yeah,
>> this is real.
>> That's how you could always tell.
>> Damn, you're raw, bro.
>> Wait, so
what is what is the last name Tom Asian?
I've always wondered.
>> Tom Asian.
>> Yeah,
>> that's a It could have a hyphen, but it
doesn't.
>> Are you Tom or you Asian? What are you?
>> Yeah, exactly. No, they uh you know,
funny enough, I I'm I'm one quarter
Armenian.
That's where I get my Yeah, that's where
I get my name from.
>> Bro, if you're Armenian, I'm Chinese,
bro.
>> You can always You can always tell in
Armenian. You just can't tell them very
much.
>> I don't get it.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> I'm standing back up because I don't get
it. Um,
>> I told my babysitter to shake her money
maker.
>> Now you have babies?
>> Yeah.
>> What is going on?
>> Don't do this, Bashar, by the way. Cuz I
told my baby sitter to shake her money
maker.
>> You don't?
>> And now she's in jail.
Oh
>> yeah.
>> Shake her money maker.
>> Yeah.
>> She's a baby maker.
>> Mhm.
>> Oh, because she makes she sits on
babies.
>> And my baby's dead.
>> Oh, right. Right. Right. Yeah. I've you
know, I heard of cake sitting, but never
babysitting.
>> A babysitter. Yeah. Okay.
>> Cake sitting.
>> A big cakes sitting fan, by the way.
>> Okay. Do you take care of livestock?
>> No, no, no. Cakes.
>> Oh, cakes.
>> Yeah. Sit on them.
>> Cakes.
>> Makes people horny.
>> You ever You ever weigh yourself?
>> Yeah. every week
>> and then and then take a poo.
>> No, before after poo.
>> And then your scales all covered in poo.
>> No.
>> No. I've never pooed on
>> only you.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Here's the thing. Morgan, you got to
poop first.
>> Yeah. Go. Yeah. I mean, just just get in
the bathroom before me if I'm ever
You're my landlord, I guess. No,
>> that's the or housemate.
>> Can I share a secret?
>> Am I perfect? No.
>> Am I trying to be better? No.
>> All right. Awesome. You're good. You're
good. What did you do today, Margan?
>> Uh, I drained a hot tub.
>> Oh,
>> yeah.
>> It's pretty handy.
>> Now, you got to you got to siphon it.
You know how you start a siphon?
>> You suck it.
>> You suck. Yes. You suck and you suck and
you suck.
>> I was going to call my girlfriend over.
>> Oh my god.
>> She wasn't home. She had to work
>> not to drain the hot tub.
>> Yeah. So, I drained the hot tub. I
respect women. I respect drained it. I
cleaned it.
>> Yeah. It's great. You know, I got Now I
got a nice clean hot tub.
>> Yeah. It was I don't know about that
though.
>> But yeah, my girlfriend got a haircut
recently.
>> Oh yeah.
>> And she hates it and and she's really
mad and and I was like, "Hey babe,
>> you don't you're just too sensitive. You
know, you you'll get over it. I'm the
one that's got to find a new
girlfriend."
>> Oh,
>> did you Wait, did you you told her that?
>> Well, like I cut her hair.
>> Oh, good.
>> Yeah. Like she didn't like it.
Don't do that. If you're if you're a
boyfriend and you she ever asks you to
cut her hair.
>> Yeah.
>> Don't do it.
>> Can I tell you a secret?
>> Yeah.
>> Um in front of God and everyone here,
I'm uh reclaiming my virginity.
>> Oh, yeah. Cool, man. Right on. How's
that?
>> Um well, I'll let you know.
>> Oh, okay.
>> I'm also I'm also reclaiming my c I'm
becoming I'm claiming celibacy.
Um, I've been celebrating since last
September
>> and I'm just waiting until someone wants
to hook up with me again.
>> Okay. Yeah, that that might work out.
You shouldn't be too long though.
>> No [ __ ]
>> You go outside.
>> We have one minute, bro. You go outside.
>> We have one minute.
>> One minute. One minute.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Make it a good one.
>> All right, man. Oh, man. Okay.
>> Um, [ __ ] bro. You carry you.
>> How's this? I got a new idea for a sushi
restaurant.
>> It's um
>> it's sushi but they play jazz there all
the time.
>> Holy [ __ ]
>> So they call it miso horny.
>> No, I've been to that place. It's called
>> You've been to Misorn.
>> We can't we can't plug other businesses
here. Sorry. Pay Coffee Bar. They sell
sushi now.
>> All right.
>> Are we uh Is that it?
>> Bye. All right. Thanks everybody.
Great job, guys.
>> Keep it going for Morgan and Jamie,
ladies and gentlemen. Morgan, Jamie.
>> All right, so the key to having a good
double set is uh listen to each other.
We're trying to have a conversation. No,
good job. You guys did great. Um little
little shoehorning with material, but we
figured it out. You guys got a groove.
I'm proud of you. Uh, online viewers,
keep it up. Keep up the good work. I'm
loving the comments. You guys are
talking some good [ __ ] Love it. Ladies
and gentlemen, some of us cannot
distinguish these next two comedians
from each other. So, I decided not to
separate them, but to put them side by
side so you can see the startling
differences in contrast in real time.
Ladies and gentlemen, I don't know who
is who. Jackson Bayine and Shane Nelson.
Hello, I'm Jackson.
>> Hi, I'm Tall Shane.
>> Now I'm Shane. Jackson, get down. Switch
sides.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> Hello, I'm Shane Nelson and this is
Jackson.
>> You guys remember those like can you
spot the difference games?
>> First off, we don't even look that much
alike. Yeah, we got mustaches and long
hairs and we don't wash our balls, but
>> we do wash our balls. We do. We do. We
do. Yeah, we wash each other's balls.
Thank you very much. But on that note,
you will notice that there's no one
sitting at this table because it smells
like balls over here for some reason. Am
I right?
>> Am I right? All right. What do those
fries taste like? Balls.
Uh I went to Jackson's house recent Went
to Jackson's house recently. Jackson,
you want to tell everyone what kind of
bed you sleep in?
>> Ball? No, it's a
ball bed. A bean bag ball, dude. Okay,
let's go. Stop. Sorry.
>> I was just about to tell them.
>> Okay, tell them.
>> No, you go.
>> Do you ever go to someone's house and
they have a giant bean bag and like you
want to sit on it cuz it looks comfy,
but you know they're [ __ ] on it.
>> I'm just jerking on it. That's all I do.
>> Or they're jerking [ __ ] on a bean
bag.
>> Yeah. Which is why I don't go to your
house and sit on your bean bag cuz
you're [ __ ] jerking off all the time,
dude.
Someone's got to do it.
>> Tell them about your bed. My bed. Well,
in my defense of my bed, I want to be
going to bed really, really fast.
>> And so, the best way to do this, have a
race car bed. Jackson sleeps in a
[ __ ] race car bed, dude. California
king.
When you get bigger like me, you'll have
to sleep in a hearse,
>> right?
>> Yeah. You're not fun. The sleep that you
never wake up from, right? That's a deep
sleep. Glad you guys are having fun.
>> That one was just right on the
>> Jackson. What's a What's your favorite
type of sex and your favorite position?
>> Depends if the dog's in the room cuz
then I get to show off.
>> Limno is the elf of the pack. Yeah. Then
I start sniffing her ass.
Sniffing her ass. You're like, "This is
my ass. I'm pissing here. This I piss on
this bed."
>> And then as soon as you leave, the dog's
pissing on your bed. He's like, "Fuck
that bitch." That's how I refill my race
car.
>> He's pissing on the tire of your race
car bed.
>> Uh, my favorite type of sex position is
In-N-Out animal style.
Hey, thank you.
>> Do we give Russian doll vibes, you
think?
>> Cuz I can fit inside of him.
>> Split me open. And there's Jackson.
>> Prove it.
>> Dude, I had to tape my nipples when I
wear a fishnet on here. We can't prove
it. When I think of Russian doll, I
think of Jackson's girlfriend.
>> Why? Not your actual girlfriend. I'm
talking about the blowup doll right next
to your bed. They bought from Russia.
>> Don't tell my girlfriend.
>> Hey, let's just look at them and see if
they uh if they feel anything.
>> Who we looking at?
>> They like us. They're not laughing, but
they're paying attention. That's good.
You two in the back. You guys kind of
look like brothers. Uh, what's your
relationship?
>> We're husband.
>> Husbands.
>> Like, are you going inside him? Like a
Russian doll. Kind of husbands.
>> Who's splitting who open?
>> I was going to say, who's the small
doll? Yeah. Who's the small doll? Stand
up. Go inside each other.
>> You're the small doll.
>> Okay. All right.
>> I can see it. I can see it.
>> What else we got? Who's a small doll in
this relationship?
>> Are you running at Joel?
>> Yeah,
>> I think we know who's going inside who.
Uh Joel's getting split open.
>> Yeah, I was going to say.
>> Well, what else is going on? Do they
like us in the chat?
>> No.
>> They don't like us.
>> Hey, vote for us in the chat, sons of
[ __ ]
>> Dude, where's my joke?
>> Dude, where's my joke? Oh, Nar, dude.
All right. All right. All right. We'll
bring a joke.
>> I smelled that.
I'm going to turn this way now. Here.
Let's go butt to butt.
>> Actually, that's back to butt. My back.
My butt's on his back.
>> It is. Bend over, dude.
This is weird, right? This is weird.
>> Yeah. You guys love it.
>> Asian girls in the back. What's up?
>> All right. All right. Yeah, they made it
less weird. I promise.
>> Yeah, dude. I know how to Don't give me
the X, dude. This is not [ __ ] Pawn
Stars. I've actually never seen Pawn
Stars.
>> You've never SEEN PAWN STARS?
>> NO, DUDE. I don't have cable.
>> I thought our dad showed us both Pawn
Stars.
>> Which reminds me, Jax and I, back when
he was single, we used to go out to the
bars together and we would pull mad
chicks, dude. Chicks love [ __ ] dudes
>> that are also brothers.
>> Yeah. We would pretend to be brothers.
And one time we pulled sisters. I swear
to God.
>> Yeah. And one time I pretended to be his
dad and we pulled a mom and a daughter.
>> And you're probably wondering who had
who?
>> Yeah. I was the daughter. He's his mom.
>> I see you're picking your teeth. That's
good.
>> What? You get anything, bud?
>> Not yet.
>> Not yet. You got something stuck in
there that's going to be on your mind.
>> We're going to get tangled getting out
of this stage.
>> Here. Reverse it. Reverse it. Reverse
it. Reverse it.
All right.
>> One more. Reverse it. Reverse it.
>> Come back around.
>> And then one more time. Reverse it. No.
No. No. Don't.
>> Come.
>> You guys want anything else from us?
>> No, I don't think they do.
>> I don't think they do.
>> Kiss. All right, we'll kiss.
DON'T
>> HE'S a skateboarder. He'll kiss me. My
name's Jackson Bay.
>> And he's Jackson Bayine. Have a good
night, everyone.
That was loud.
>> You ever open a pack of baseball cards
and get the same player twice in a row
and you're like, "Come on, what the
fuck?" That's what that felt like. You
got like two same Pokemons. I got two
Digletts. Two Digletts. [ __ ] One more
time for Shane and Jackson, ladies and
gentlemen. Keep it going for those two.
Um, so if you thought that last duo was
[ __ ] this next duo is definitely
[ __ ] No, they're they're two comics
that are dating each other. Um, not like
Russian doll, I guess. Kind of Russian.
You be the judge. Ladies and gentlemen,
coming to the stage, Joel Huitt and Abby
Rose.
Hello everybody.
>> All right, that was a mild response.
Like that.
>> Uh, hey guys. What's up? I'm Joel Euans.
>> Abby Rose.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Uh, we are very happily in love.
>> Yeah. Um,
>> and happy to be here.
>> Very happy to be here. We're both from
North Carolina.
>> Uh, yeah. There's some North Kakalakians
in here. I like that. It's funny how two
people can be from the same part of the
world and go halfway across the world to
find each other in love.
>> Love you, babe.
>> Yeah, there's a there's actually a lot
of similarities between Hawaii and North
Carolina. You know, you can rock a
mullet, there's country living,
you can get away with dating your
cousin.
>> Best cousin ever. [ __ ] EVERYBODY GIVE
IT UP FOR MY FAVORITE cousin Joel Huins.
Everybody.
Yeah. Speaking of mullets,
this guy [ __ ] got a mullet after we
started dating. He copied me basically
and now he gets all the credit. Every
time Chino introduces him to the stage,
it's always give it up for this guy with
the best hair. It's always so quafted
and then it's and then give it up for
the mulleted girlfriend. No, he's the
mulleted boyfriend. I had the mullet
first. Just so Just so that's clear.
>> You know what though? It It all works
out because when we make love, you can't
tell where my mullet begins and her
mullet ends. You know what I mean? It's
like Avatar where they have hair sex.
Dude, it's so intense. It's like a
Kentucky waterfall of ecstasy.
It's incredible. We look like a We look
like a couple made in the back of a
pickup truck. It's a It's an amazing
thing, you know. I got a mullet. She's
got a mullet. This means that Abby has
two mullets, right? Uh we're on social
media. Give us a follow if you like. Uh
I have a social media. I have an
Instagram. She has an Instagram. So,
this means that Abby has two Instagrams.
You know what I mean? And my birthday is
6 days after hers. So, this means that
Abby has, say with me now,
>> two birthdays, right?
>> Uh, Aby's birthday is April 20th, 420.
Any stoners in the house?
>> Yeah.
>> That's also Hitler's birthday.
>> And, uh, let me take an opportunity.
Yeah, there's one guy. Let me take an
opportunity to tell you the similarities
between my girlfriend and Adolf Hitler.
All right. They are both obsessed
with death and genocide, right? Adolf
Hitler wanted to kill all the Jews.
>> Abby here wants to kill every woman that
I follow on social.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Joel likes to speak
in extremes, everybody. That's not true.
That's not accurate. But you know what?
Speaking of Instagram,
>> I'm going to I'm going to I wonder what
everybody has to think about this.
Honestly, I'm going to tell everybody
right now. I've been noticing this [ __ ]
Angie like your Instagram posts. So, who
the [ __ ] is Angie? Who the [ __ ] Angie?
>> Angie? Angie is my mother.
You know your aunt,
your father's sister. She was there when
we met. You don't remember that?
>> Maybe I remember.
>> Yeah. Okay. I'm I'm sorry.
>> Yeah.
>> You're still my favorite cousin.
>> That's great.
>> Yeah.
>> That's good stuff. That's really good
stuff. Um, you know what does it for me
about you, dear?
The way that you burp at random whenever
we're having heated conversation. It's
really good.
That's so
>> Yeah, I think that's so
>> what else does it for you?
>> You know what else really does it for
me? The way that whenever we have
relationship problems, you decide to
consult Chat GPT.
>> Is that what you think?
>> Yeah.
>> Is that
>> That's probably the number one thing
that I wish I could change about you. If
anything
>> is chat GPT
>> is the fact that you talk to Jav TPT
about our relationship. And the one
thing that you wish you could change
about me is probably that I fart during
sex. Right.
>> That's one thing.
>> It's good. It's good. Everyone in this
room now knows that I fart during sex.
Uh
>> what was your impressions of my mother?
>> When you met her?
>> Your mother?
>> Yeah. You both You both have uh a
certain kind of tattoo, right?
>> We both have a tram stamp.
>> Yes. You and my mother both have [ __ ]
stamps. It's the one common ally. My
mother My mother is married to a pastor
of 40 years and she has a tram stamp. I
just want that to be known for the
internet and everybody watching.
>> That's what I got. Uh, is there anything
about our trip to North Carolina you
wanted to talk about?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. We recently went back to North
Carolina to meet each other's families
and lately I've been having some cat
issues and my cat pissed on Joel.
>> Yep. And then we go on this vacation or
whatever and his friend's cat pisses all
over my suitcase and then we go to my
sister's and then her cat [ __ ] what
does her cat do?
>> Her cat attacks me. Uh tries to [ __ ]
me and then uh then your your
brother-in-law grabbed him with an oven
mitt and stuffed him into a trash can if
I remember correctly.
>> I think it was a cage but
>> Okay.
>> It's great. It's good stuff. All right,
babe. We got anything else?
>> Well, yeah. The other day, um, we were
smoking
>> and I asked you
if when you eat asparagus,
your pee smells like asparagus, what
happens when you eat asparagus and you
squirt?
>> Why do you [ __ ] ask chat GPT?
>> That's insane.
>> GPT. Can somebody Can somebody chat GPT
if your squirt will smell like asparagus
if you eat enough of it?
>> Squirt speed, right?
>> All right, guys. We're out of here.
Thank you.
>> Keep it going for the lovely couple,
Joel and Abby Rose. Ladies and
gentlemen,
>> this microphone smells like a Mumford
and Sun song. What the hell just
happened?
Boom. Clap. Yeah. I feel like you guys
would make great
>> Yeah. music. You guys should Someone get
a guitar, get a tambourine. One of you
shave your head. You got a great act
going. All right. This next act. Can't
wait to get on stage. And I can't wait
to bring them up. Two from last week and
the past two weeks. Back for a third.
Ladies and gentlemen, give Sasha and
Craig.
>> Thank you, Chino.
Are there two mics? Oh, that's good. We
don't have to share.
>> I'm bad at sharing. I'm probably going
to be bad at this to be honest. I don't
play well with others. It's why I'm
doing comedy cuz I'm unlikable.
>> She said to me, she said to me when I
first Well, she said it on stage, too.
She's like, I'm on the apps, the dating
apps. I was like, "Oh, my method is I
just go to Safeway and look for eye
contact in the produce section."
>> I feel that's a very 70s way to meet
somebody. And I do respect that. I feel
like that was the decade. I'm sorry I
missed.
>> The truth to that joke is that at the
marina in San Francisco, there is a
night one night a week that is singles
night. Anyway, just telling you.
>> Okay. Anybody else on the apps here? Are
you all okay? Thank you. Yeah. Or you're
all just like the couple that was here
and they're like all happy and [ __ ]
>> I don't know how you're gonna be a
comedian if you're happy. It just
doesn't work that way. I'm sorry.
Last time I was here, you know, people
online like to make insults. Sometimes
they strike comedy gold. This one guy
said, "That guy looks like he eats beer.
You should put that on your dating
profile.
>> It's a selling point.
>> I was thinking after you talked about
being on the apps, I should probably get
on them. You know what I mean?
>> I mean, it's very interesting and you
know, if I have ghosted you know
>> on one of the apps. I'm very sorry.
That's probably how most people on Maui
recognize me at this point.
>> I I do apologize. It It wasn't you. I
just get very anxious,
you know, about talking to strangers.
But I I am I am in a long-distance
relationship now. And so far, he hasn't
asked me to invest in Bitcoin. So, it's
going really well,
>> I think.
>> But he has sent you,
>> dickpicks.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. That's why we're still talking.
>> Yeah. And so my my best friend's gay and
my understanding is this is actually how
gay relationships start is first you
exchange dickpicks and then you meet up
and have sex and then if you kind of
like each other after that then you
might start dating. So you know it's all
a little bit in reverse to straight
people but it it's kind of more fun.
It's better that way.
>> I uh I've been calling this the hair of
unemployment since the fire. I haven't
been working, but I I got a job with
this hair. Anyway, uh now I'm a guy with
a job and a car, which is a certain
standard that's important.
>> Put that on the side.
I know about that.
>> Looking for a person with a job and a
car.
>> Job, car, you have a face, you can go
out in public.
Uh, I would put it back, but one of my
least favorite insults
were all the insults pertaining to me
putting this in a ponytail comparing me
to Steven Seagull.
>> I did not enjoy those.
>> I mean, okay. Well, I guess nowadays
it's an insult. When I was growing up in
the '9s, that was like every weekend was
going to see a Steven Seagal movie. Um,
so, you know, that might have been a
compliment at some point. Like maybe
they think that you're trying to save
the the nature preserve from the evil
oil company. Maybe that that's what
they're saying. They're not saying that
like you're some weirdo who's hiding out
in Russia.
Oh, I mean I understand when you're
looking at me, you thinking that guy
should lose some weight. I agree. Uh but
I've been on this diet that I really
like. It's called the add cheese diet.
You just add cheese to everything and of
course it makes it better.
>> I fully support that diet.
>> Uh, shoot. Uh, so I got a lifeguard
joke. I got two lifeguard friends in the
audience.
I must tell it again.
Ever since I became a lifeguard at a
pool, I became really, really good at
looking to the left,
looking to the right.
Then look to the left again.
>> Very good at that.
>> Oh, all right. We having fun. So
sometimes when I I walk across a parking
lot cuz locally we got these beautiful
trucks, you know, they're like 30,
$40,000 trucks on 50, $60,000
suspensions.
And I stop and stare. I admit it. Right.
So I like to just stop talk to some
local guy. Hey, should I be embarrassed
to admit? I like to look under the
skirts of other men's trucks. Oh, have
you seen those front ends? They're so
beautiful. And then the guy goes, "Oh,
me, too. And have you seen the rear
ends, bro?"
That's my truck joke. Anyway, I like I
like looking at other people's big
trucks, but they're like a really
expensive girlfriend. I'm glad you got
one. I like looking at her, but uh I
don't want one for myself.
>> Yeah. I I really know nothing about
trucks. When I see those kind of trucks,
the lifted ones, I I'm a huge nerd, so
I'm just like, that looks like a really
disappointing transformer. Like, it
looks like it's about to transform into
something cool, but then it never does.
Uh, huge disappointment. Can't I can't
get on board with the trucks. I'm sorry.
It's It's very uncool of me as a person
born and raised on Maui to not like
those trucks. But
>> yeah, I love my Toyota car.
gets like 35 miles to the gallon.
>> Yeah, that's a big dick car.
The more sensible the car, the bigger
the dick. The more ridiculous the
vehicle, the smaller the dick. And it's
always true. It's like ladies, like
you're looking for a guy in a Prius.
Trust me.
God, this girl is so awesome. Oh my god,
it's so cool. Anyway, shoot. So, I'm in
a ceramics class. If I may recommend you
go, if you want to be cool, okay, you
you go to school. The community college
is amazing. I'm taking a ceramics class.
I'm getting my hands on some clay for
the first time. And I just realized, oh,
I really want to ask my teacher if I can
if I can try to construct a vagina in
clay. Not that there's anything wrong
with that or I just I just want to ask
her that now that I thought of it.
>> I'm not sure if I really want to even do
it. I just want to ask her that.
>> Yeah, you can make one of those cups
like they have on the International
Space Station. Has anybody seen the
coffee cups that they have on the
International Space Station? They they
literally look like [ __ ] And it's
because it allows you to drink coffee in
zero gravity without it spilling all
over you. I'm not kidding. Google it.
Uh, you know, for some reason my
Instagram feed when things look like
dicks and [ __ ] they always show up
in the feed and then I go straight to
the comments to see how many people said
that it looked like a dick or [ __ ] and
then everybody does. And then there's
always one person that's like real
mature. everybody.
But it does. It looks like a [ __ ]
>> So, uh,
what do you think? How many How many
minutes have we used?
>> Got two minutes left.
>> 2 minutes left.
>> What you think?
>> 8 minutes.
>> I got one.
>> That's impressive.
>> I got one thing I'd like to share with
you.
>> Put that on the profile.
>> Have you uh Have you heard of this thing
called earththing? Have you heard of
earththing?
>> Earththing. You know when you touch your
feet to the ground, you're connected
electrically.
>> Oh, that's some like hippie white people
[ __ ]
>> Yeah.
>> Well, you are
continue.
>> When Paltro is a big believer speak.
>> Oh, does she sell it on goop?
>> Anyway, so the idea is if you're you if
you don't have rubber between yourself
and the earth that it's good for you,
right? It's uh you're electrically
connected like a grounded wire. So,
that's this idea. There's a movie about
it. Whatever. I don't know. I don't
know. Anyway, if if it's true
that just like touching the earth with
your feet is good for you, right?
>> Okay.
>> Then like if you jump into the water in
the ocean, the pool, a lake, a stream,
then that's kind of like making love to
the planet.
>> I mean, you're going to get an STD.
>> You're touching the earth on every
millimeter of your body. So, it's got to
be the healthiest thing ever. I mean to
the planet though like at the very least
the earth has the clap. I'm sorry. Like
you know wear a rubber if you're gonna
the staff infection might be.
>> Okay.
>> But I think it's kind of Anyway, so that
joke may not be funny right now but when
you get in the water in the future if
you think oh it's like making love to
the planet an angel gets its wings. And
if that happens like a year from now
then freaking right on. Anyway,
>> don't you have like a water thing going
on
>> at airport?
>> Oh, yeah. Sophie. Okay. So, yeah, thanks
for thanks for thanks for putting up
with us. Uh the Sophie swim is next
Sunday at Airport Beach. If you want to
do a good thing, if you can swim a mile,
come on down and swim a mile and hang
out.
>> It's right in front of the West End. So,
you can annoy all the tourists that were
like, I paid $1,000 to be here and now
all the locals are here ruining it. ruin
things for tourists. And unless you are
a tourist, then I'm I'm sorry. Welcome
to Maui.
>> All right. Aloha. Thank you everybody.
Well, and I got a YouTube channel called
All Good Things and All Good Time. I got
7,000 subscribers. I'm trying to get to
eight, maybe uh 10. Get that black.
Keep it going for Sasha and Craig.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you want more of that and you're
single, check your local dating apps.
That's what's waiting for you. All
right. You got one man, one one woman.
You know, depending what you're looking
for, that's what's in the singles list.
Everybody who's in a relationship right
now is just like, "Oh, thank God."
Breathing a sigh of relief. I know it's
tough here on my from what I hear. I
don't really know. I'm doing just fine.
All right. Uh I'm going to walk around
uh with the tip bucket in just a second.
Real quick, want to give a shout out to
our show sponsor, ladies and gentlemen.
Highspice hot sauce.
That's right. Handmade, locally grown
hot sauce made here on the island of
Maui. I can say handcrafted cuz it's
these hands that craft them. If you want
my hands in your mouth, get my hot
sauce. I should change that tagline. You
can find it anywhere locally. Uh you can
find at Monof Foods right down the
street. Check us out at the farmers
market, swap meat, or on the website.
Type in coms sim10 on icepice.com to get
10% off your order and give us credit
for this order. Uh like and subscribe
all the online viewers. All right, we're
going to keep it moving right along. We
got some more comedians coming to the
stage right now. We have a very special
guest, a comic joining us all the way
from Los Angeles, one of my friends, as
well as one of our local comics that you
all know, the Birdman, Eddie V and Aaron
Guette. Keep it going.
Don't want no short mic stand. Don't
want no short mic stand. Itsybitsy
teensyweensy short mic stand. Hey, give
it up for Aaron coming back for a year.
It's been a year. We were We were all
the way up at Story last time you were
here, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. New you guys.
>> We're going to be doing jokes and
probably some roasting. So,
>> let me make myself more roastable. We
also really want to mix it up because
the last I mean all the couples so far
have had the same haircut. So I just,
you know, perfect.
>> I'm more roastable.
>> I'm more roastable now.
>> And you wake up roastable. I mean, funny
thing is we both work on rooftops
but in very different capacities. I was
realizing that. Like you keep people dry
and I'm a bartender. So it's
>> Oh. Yeah, she works at a rooftop bar. I
didn't know that. That's good.
>> Um,
>> that's [ __ ] boring. Moving on.
>> Aaron Aaron came all the way from LA to
to to do to do a a Latina dance festival
in Honolulu. And I'm just thinking that
she's trying to like put some color in
her gan pool,
>> you know? Let's read the comments right
now.
She looks like she might have as many
possibly as many diet plans as
therapists.
>> I don't know.
>> Well, you look like you escaped the set
of the Vikings TV show and we're like,
let's make it Beach Bum, you know? Let's
>> maybe no one will notice me.
>> Right. She She went to Turtle Town to
have a whole new experience and then
went to the west side to throw rocks at
seals.
>> Actually, I went on a run and almost
stepped on a sea turtle.
>> Like I almost full on all my body weight
landed on one cuz it was right there and
I was like, "Fuck, I must have committed
like a horrible felony." Do you guys
have like the the wildlife? Somehow you
have managed this is genius. You guys
have managed to wrangle the wildlife to
work for your government, right? Cuz the
fees are crazy, right? If you get within
six feet of a sea turtle, is that right?
>> Yes. I think it's 12 feet or something.
>> But they're always coming to you. Have
you noticed that? They're always they're
trying. It's like it's like our meter
maze in LA,
>> right?
>> You know,
>> so so uh she she lives in WeHo and I was
in WeHo and uh I looked for three days
and I never found
a little person prostitute the whole
time.
>> The broken dolphin, everyone. The broken
dolphin.
>> Step into the light. It will not hurt
you.
>> Yeah, that does. I've heard that before.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> We've heard that one. That was
>> Walk into the light, my child.
>> That was not triggering at all. Um,
>> are you are you doing okay? Are you hung
over? What's going with the sunglasses?
Also, why did you steal those from my
mom in Orange County? Well, I So, a
little a little thing is these these
glasses were $6 and I just had Cadillac
or cataract surgery, but it
>> Cadillac surgery,
>> but but but it was done in Japan, so I
think it's Cadillac surgery. And it
worked. I haven't bought a Cadillac yet.
At my age, everybody owns a Cadillac.
>> Did it work? Based on that word slip up,
I'm not sure. I don't know. We'll see
when the side effects go away,
>> right? We'll we'll see what's happening.
Um, so, so how tell what what's your
where are you from? What's your
bloodline? What
>> what is my bloodline? Wow. I thought
where are you from? What do you you're
like social security number. Um,
step into the light. This is a lot. Uh,
my bloodline is uh it's mostly German
actually. You can tell when I sneeze.
>> Fargan pretty much. It's like it's very
intense. Um,
>> yeah. No, I don't sneeze like most girls
are like like the broken sprinkler
>> out here. We sneeze like
>> No, that's just you.
>> Oh,
>> but yeah, I'm that. I'm an Eastern
European, which is why everyone thinks
I'm Russian.
>> Ah,
>> also because I worked with teenagers and
they permanently damaged my face.
>> So, you just have resting this [ __ ]
face all the time?
>> No, it's Russian [ __ ] face.
>> Oh, okay. I'm not Russian. I'm Dutch.
>> Stupid. Um,
>> wait. Is that what is that how they is
that how they speak? Is that where the
broken dolphin comes from?
>> No, they speak more like pigeon English.
>> So, animal noises. So, I wasn't too far.
>> No, that's that's
>> the birdman. Everyone,
>> when I'm trying to pick someone up,
that's what I do. And then I usually
walk away. It's terrible. IT WORKS FOR
THE PIGEONS. THEY'RE
>> That doesn't work. No.
I was shocked.
>> No, it did work one time and I've used
it ever since. And it hasn't worked.
>> I mean, I know your daughter, so I know
it's worked.
>> Right.
>> Fun fact, I grew up with birds.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Yeah, I accidentally starved all of
them.
>> Technically, I blame my mom for this.
She's a burer. She Okay. You know how
like every white woman after menopause
becomes obsessed with birds? It's just a
biological thing that happens. She will
like send me videos of birds that she's
rescued from their natural habitats.
It's getting out of hand. Like she
>> So So she's she's got birds on life
support.
>> Well, she thinks she's put them on life
support, but she like Okay, so like she
sent me a video of this hummingbird,
right? And she's like, "It was too tired
to drink water, but it was really
parched." So I took it in and I got it
to drink water and then it finally
slept. But she like she sent a video she
she waterboarded the hummingbird.
>> Oh my god.
>> I had to tell her I was like, "Please
get a hobby." And then she got into
musical theater and like just started
Mary Poppins as Guess Who?
It
>> was like a moment of karma for my mom.
She was the bird lady.
>> Oh, okay.
>> You know, the feed the birds.
>> So, if we were on a date and I wanted to
like I got the ick somehow, I would say
>> somehow by like the 30-year age gap,
maybe.
>> No, I would be like I would be like,
"Dude, I bet your mom's super hot."
>> Would that work?
>> You know what? I think Can I help you
with your pickup lines, Eddie? Cuz
>> anytime I'm I'm wide open. I feel like
we've got room for grope.
>> Room for grope.
>> That's a new business plan for me,
right? Pick up lines for comics.
>> No hope, room for grope.
>> Do you I'd love to be a dating coach for
comedians.
>> I it I mean I I look at Aaron and I'm
like, is it is it Ukraine and Russia
like they had a baby?
>> No, they're at war.
>> No, but I mean
>> they also had a baby. And that is kind
of what I do look like. I'm at war and
unified at the same time.
>> That's why I think
>> does make sense.
>> It was like a little twist on
>> something about this
>> like like I think I think Zalinski and
and and Putin I think they're just gay
and they just need to like just get get
together like they just need
>> most politicians do.
>> Right. That's true. So how how is the
political climate in in in California?
Things good? Are are you still hanging
out at, you know, Skid Row and checking
out the fentanyl scene and all that good
stuff?
>> I, you know, I've never done that. Okay.
But how was it when you tried it?
>> Uh, I make sure I run through every
time. There's always some fun to be had.
>> Well, you could get some secondhand
substance abuse if you don't run
through.
>> True. And some secondhand smoke.
>> A little dabble. Do you right, Chino?
No.
All right. Well, you know, I really
enjoy So,
>> this this gal right here, she runs the
Deadpan show. So,
>> if you're ever running through, check
her out.
>> Also, because I do like uh um
appropriate culture of comedy, I do run
a show is a salsa comedy show called
Last Comic Dancing.
>> Just took it to Australia, so maybe I'll
bring it here sometime. But
>> yes, that'd be cool.
>> Anyway, it's good to be back.
>> It's good to see you.
>> Nice. Yeah, it's great to see you.
>> I I do have one last question for you.
>> Okay.
>> What happened to that cat before you
murdered it?
>> Oh. Um I
>> This cat I I dropped acid
>> in the cat's.
>> No, in the cat's water and the cat has
never recovered.
>> It looks like you dropped acid in the
cat's eye drops. That's what it That's
what it looks like.
>> All right. Well, this has been fun.
>> This has been amazing. Thank you. Thanks
for having
>> chat. We can't wait to read the cesspool
of comments.
>> So excited.
>> Keep it going for Aaron and Eddie,
ladies and gentlemen.
>> It was funny. Somebody in the comment
section was like, "Are they dating?" And
then you pointed out the age gap, and I
was like, "I think he should date her
mom. That sounds pretty hot, right?
After Where's mama at? I don't know.
Could be could be exciting. The internet
is now invested. They want to know what
happens from here. All right. Uh,
someone named Ye
signed up. Who is that? Is that you?
Okay. Hold on. Hold on, partner.
Breaking the rules.
>> I just wanted to identify you. Um, we
got like one, two, two more left and
we'll get you up. You cool?
>> Cool. That cool. I just want to make
sure cuz I I didn't know that was you.
Right on. All right. Uh, by the way,
this list is almost full. If anybody
else wants to come up here and do a duo
set, uh, he doesn't have a partner, so
if anybody wants to join him, I'll allow
it. [ __ ] that could be fun. That could
be weird. Who knows what kind of first
date situation? No, not yet. Not yet.
See soon.
>> We'll get you a partner.
>> Yeah, we got we got a couple more
comments.
>> Make fun of me.
>> Oh, no. No. I was just confirming cuz I
didn't know. I was not familiar with the
name. Unfamiliar name. Just got to
double check. All right, we'll get Edge
up here soon. coming to the stage right
now. We got uh the return of a comedian
who hasn't joined us for a while and
then our comment moderator uh comment
section knows him of his Jimbo and Mr.
John Cay.
>> What up, Pa?
>> What's up, guys? Give it up for Pa Bay
Coffee Bar. Give it up for the the staff
at the bar.
>> No, you're right. We're not We're not
doing Let's get after the people not
paying attention the whole show at the
bar. What up?
>> Bar people. Bar people. WHAT UP?
>> YOU HAVE TO JOIN this fever dream with
us. Okay.
>> YOU DON'T GET TO CHECK OUT AND NOT
experience the hell that happens up
here. That's why your burger is only
$30.
>> I don't know. What's up, John?
>> Uh, you know, uh, been busy, been
working a lot. You know, I I'm a tour
guide. Uh, so I work a lot and I meet a
lot of tourists and I realize I I'm
actually pretty judgmental. Uh, but I
meet I meet about 10 new people a day
and I really get to know them over 10
hours. And I don't judge these people,
but I found out I judge people because
on my day off, which I treasure, I go to
Costco.
>> And I judge people based on what they
have in their cart. John, are you
running a [ __ ] two-minute bid on me
right now? I'm going to lose my [ __ ]
>> I'm in the audience with you guys
listening to John's joke. Continue.
Oh, I was hoping
>> Put your manifesto away. Calm down.
>> Okay. All right. All right. All right.
>> Why do white men that look like him
always have to have a book? Why? What is
that?
>> It's a fair point. You know, something
that I think Jimbo and I both have in
common is that we look like a TSA agent
who's already decided who we're going to
randomly search.
>> John's me before I gave up.
>> John's like holding on to the last straw
that I saw 5 years ago. So, this is what
I have to look forward to is way worse.
>> Bombing in Minnesota.
>> I did I did
>> I did bomb in Minnesota. Um I went
>> in the Middle East, guys.
>> Yeah, I was in the Middle East. In
Minnesota, I um That's the Midwest. Ohio
is the Middle East.
>> Oh, sorry. Your geography, right? I was
in Minnesota recently and I did realize.
Is anyone from Minnesota in here?
>> One escapee. Sick. I was in Minnesota.
There's not as many Somalians as they
say there are in there. I'm just telling
you guys, boots on the ground. I would
say there's the perfect amount of
Somalians there.
>> I realize no matter how I say that,
>> how many Somalians is it?
>> I don't know. Everyone's got their own
level for me. Perfect. I don't know.
It's
>> terrible. That's as racist as I'll get
tonight.
>> Why is that the funniest joke I told
him?
>> Jimbo seems like the kind of guy that
would know a lot about Lindsay Clancy
and surprisingly not a lot about Andrew
Tate.
>> I know more about Tom Clansancy. I don't
That's a dated joke for you with old
[ __ ] I don't care. I don't care what
happens in the news and court cases. I
uh I really just care when you're going
to cut your hair. That's what I It's all
that's been on my radar lately.
>> Yeah.
>> The chat's been asking. They're like,
"Jimbo, can you talk to John? We're
worried about him."
>> Sorry, guys. I'll work on it.
>> No, just cut it.
>> Or get a perm. Go all in. Don't lose one
of this half.
Perm's not a bad idea. I could do
something like her back there. That will
look good. Damn, that's some good hair.
I see what John's going for.
That's funnier than you're giving us.
Okay, that's really
>> All right, chat. You can't see her. It's
okay.
Manifesto
says
>> Joe Rogan Bible every morning. Okay,
sorry.
>> What? What? Does anyone have a guess?
Does anyone have a guess? Uh, what John
has written in that notebook?
>> Take a guess. Mustache.
>> Yeah. Addresses of women.
Anyone else also share that? That he
might have addresses of women.
>> That was my guess, too.
>> Yikes, dude.
>> Johnson. Holy [ __ ] How did they know?
>> Over. Well,
>> are you a gambler?
>> I am. Are you a gambler?
>> I I was I was
>> How much How much would you put on that
you can outdrive me?
>> Cuz I've been I've been asking I've been
requesting and it's gone unresponsive.
I've been challenging this guy to a
drive off. Oh. Oh, and golf. Oh, golf.
Okay. Yes. Um I was like driving on an
island. Not many places. Um golf. Yeah.
I I have a lot of belly here. I don't
know if he noticed that,
>> but I can sling a club. Um but I have
seen you working. John looks like he is
a golfer. done
or wanting to try to be a golfer.
>> I I did golf in a senior's only league.
>> It was senior high school women.
>> You lost
the court case cuz I don't know.
>> I hadn't started the hormones yet. Yeah.
>> Holy [ __ ] Where? I swear I was going to
get into trans sports.
>> Everyone's paying attention now. I can't
believe I asked them to pay attention to
this. This is embarrassing.
>> You brought a lot to the table for us.
>> Thank you. I I I always have a lot on my
table.
>> Me and John are so similar. Can I tell
you how similar we are? We both were
named after a white man from the Bible.
>> There's a white guy in the Bible named
Jimbo.
>> Yeah.
All right, let's get started.
>> Oh, Jimbo and the technicolor dream
coke. The dream's dead. There's no code.
He's poor homeless. It's
>> If you want a visualization of that,
just find Mr. E tonight.
>> I like how John just called me out on
gambling and then like that. We do. You
gamble, Jimbo?
You watch porn?
>> Who' you vote for? He definitely knows
how to use an incognito tab. That's for
sure.
>> Yeah.
>> Wait, I I just learned that people open
their browsers not incognito and it
bothered me.
>> I don't know how you do it. The bravery.
I don't know. I would I would not want
to see John search history. Not cuz it's
like anything bad, but
>> it would just it would just show me a
side of you that I couldn't unsee. It's
like this haircut. It's
>> Yeah. It's like a car accident. Yeah,
>> he Googles car accidents. He has a sick
fetish.
>> What else is in that book? Give us Give
us
>> You want another?
>> I do.
>> All right. Put it on my back, guys.
>> Lindsay Clancy might not have did it.
>> [ __ ]
>> Okay. So, uh I lowkey am a supporter.
That's that's that's why. Um, I think
that
I
>> I stand with the uh the 10 out of 11
jurors. I feel like that's a majority,
right?
>> Are you on the minority there?
>> Oh, I you know I really uh I in that
sense I'd like to be a minority. Uh
okay, that was that was my second racist
joke of the night.
Someone with melon cure me. I don't
know. It's terrible.
>> I realized I realized after getting to
know Jimbo a little bit better that
Lindsay Clansancy supporters are really
no different than Andrew Tate
supporters.
>> Uh she uh ended up in a wheelchair
somehow. I think that's what the case is
about.
>> I really only know Tom Clancy. I used to
play Rainbow 6 games with people in
other states and murder people. That was
what raised me. Grand Theft Auto and
Rainbow 6. This is who I am. A white
man. I'm on no list for the record.
None.
>> None.
>> No.
>> Surprising. It's all that incognito use.
>> After this set, he's going to put me on
his though, for sure.
>> You look like the guy that Adam Sandler
apologized to in Billy Madison.
Oh, Vani. I like that.
>> John doesn't Does John give off school
shooter vibes or is it just me?
Yeah,
>> but he's really politically drawn, so
it's like President shooter vibes.
>> Is that the joke that he's trans? Yes.
>> Am I proud of it? No.
>> Wouldn't be presidential then. It would
be CEO of another healthcare company. Or
who's going to be the next Charlie Kirk?
That seems like your alley.
>> The next
Charlie Kirk.
>> It's a neck joke. Sorry. We have two
minutes of this. Should we just be the
heroes of the night and not make you do
two more minutes of couples? Guys, my
name is John Kai. This is Jimbo. Thank
you so much. I love it.
>> I just want to say I love you, Chad.
That's all I care for.
>> You took the power out of Jimbo's hands.
John and Jimbo. Ladies and gentlemen,
the one who looks forward to the school
shooting and the one who looks forward
to the school pizza. Those two guys.
>> Oh, come on. Don't act like you don't
remember the square cut school pizza.
Two pepperonis. Like that wasn't enough.
>> With the chocolate milk,
>> dude. Hey, with the chocolate milk,
right? Stuffing you full of dairy at
11:15 in the morning and then sending
you back to fourth period. Try not to
[ __ ] your pants in PE, kid. That's what
it was like. All right.
We had stronger digestive systems then,
right? Can Hey, beard. And I know your
name, but for audience purposes, your
beard. When's the last time you had two
slices of pizza and a chocolate milk for
breakfast?
and didn't [ __ ] yourself.
>> Never. Maybe a birthday at best, right?
That's right. All right. No, avoid the
pizza. And And
I still think about that pizza. By the
way, guys, just so you know, I was a
corrections officer for an entire month
at MC.
If you miss Maui High Food, they still
serve it in our local jail.
You're literally two misdemeanor away
from having school breakfast again. Just
try it out. I'll see you there. All
right, we got a couple more sets. We're
coming close to the end of the night.
Don't worry, guys. I got you coming
soon. Coming up to the stage right now,
we got Mystery and Brady.
>> Keep it going for Chino. EVERYBODY,
>> what an awesome Monday night. So great
to see so many people in in PA.
>> I want to say a nice place to meet
interesting people, but I think peculiar
might be more accurate.
>> Yeah. By the way, speaking of peculiar
people, my name is Brady Sparkman. Um,
you might have seen my name come up in
the Epstein files a few times. I
I had a bit of a rough childhood. So,
you know, they weren't really good about
keeping the victims hidden. So, you
know, anyways,
victim of child molestation. Uh, what
you got going?
>> Is that the Birds of Lindsay?
>> No,
>> we're we're not there yet.
>> Getting a little uh ahead of ourselves.
I thought I was up here to help you
address your schizophrenia issues. Can
we Can we see the real you? I mean, this
I mean, where's Earl?
>> Earl,
>> I came up here to break Earl.
>> Okay. For the for the 15th time, Earl is
a is a personality I do
>> and I'm trying to break away from it,
but I you keep trying. If I
>> I don't even think the chat crowd would
recognize you as anything but Earl.
Oh, you want to do Earl now?
>> No, no, I don't. But I did say peculiar,
so why not bring it out?
>> So, [ __ ] I can't do this on like
command.
>> ALL RIGHT. GOD damn it. This is You
brought out the [ __ ] beast in me.
What? What do you want?
>> Wow.
>> Where are we going with this?
>> I don't know where to begin. I mean,
>> do you have any questions?
>> Yeah. What's your I I know you're a run
for president. What's your plans to to
uh intercept and mitigate police
brutality?
>> Are you [ __ ] serious? You wake my ass
up and you start with a question like
that. I'mma give the cops billy clubs.
That's what we're going to do with this.
No more guns. You got to earn the gun.
>> The sad truth is he's got a better
policy than Trump.
>> Probably. Well, it ain't hard to have a
better [ __ ] policy than that. That
guy just makes [ __ ] up as he goes and
then he prays that reality lines up with
it and [ __ ]
>> It's way better that you made this up
last night.
>> What?
>> It's way better that you made this up
last night.
>> I didn't make [ __ ] up. I made that up
like right now. Like
>> Fair.
>> Last night I played video games until I
[ __ ] fell asleep.
Tequila Haze. And I'm not proud of that.
But that's what happened is Red Dead
Redemption. How you gonna not drink
tequila while you [ __ ] invaded
a [ __ ] fort in Mexico?
>> Are you talking about a video game?
>> Yes.
>> Earl's a [ __ ] nerd. Okay. A lot of
people don't. I I'm a little nerd type
mentality to walk into other people's
games and realities.
>> What?
Bro, I said we ought to do DMT on stage.
Did you go?
>> Dude, I am not bringing felonies out on
live stage. I told you I'm not doing you
anything tonight.
>> That is a federal offense. And um
>> plus what's DMT?
>> Uh
>> I've never heard of dimethylryptony.
>> No, it's a
dag gone metal thrash. It's a type of
music.
>> Metal thrash. Huh. Yeah.
>> I guess that's why I don't know about
it.
>> You like headaches, don't you? Is that
why Earl comes?
>> [ __ ] love them.
>> Wow.
>> Anyways, like this Earl bit I just ain't
working. I
>> Yeah, we clearly got more attention with
DMT. I think my I think my bit I mean,
you're right. Maybe I should have
brought my DMT on stage.
>> No, you shouldn't have done that. That's
That's not a good idea.
>> Look, this is all an act. Yeah. Well, I
I had a friend
>> the DMT is not real like girls.
>> I had a friend one time light up a blunt
in front of the whole audience, which
works if you're killing it, but like he
had like seven people in the [ __ ]
audience and he just lights up a blunt
and just and you got to be cool.
>> I used to live in San Francisco and
Oakland. You can light a blunt anywhere
there.
>> Well, fair. This was in [ __ ] Lahina.
>> You know, there was a legitimate sta
legitimate comedy show where Cat
Williams was in Oakland and made it 5
minutes to y'all crack is too good and
got walked off stage.
>> That's the Bay Area
>> and [ __ ] happens.
>> You know what I got right here? This is
a cigarette.
>> I've seen them.
>> This [ __ ]
>> I don't get wet.
>> I only like good stuff. This is my
newest product. We brought it to market.
>> Dude, this actually brings me to my main
point. I thought maybe if you started
getting some better esteem so that bump
maybe you'd be a little less
schizophrenic.
>> I don't do LSD, buddy.
>> That might be the problem.
>> Fair.
I'm honestly I'm listening. That sounds
like a good
>> You ever heard of orange sunshine?
And it's better than my [ __ ] doctor.
>> It's not even LSD in your hand. It
doesn't turn to LSD till it hits your
stomach. So you could say you're not
holding OSD and you're not even lying.
>> Okay. But I like lying to authorities.
>> You are running for president. So
>> absolutely. By the way, I am running for
president, but I wasn't going to
announce that yet. I was working on a
campaign.
>> I wish I could say for the chess club,
but we all know he doesn't play chess.
Well, [ __ ] I figure I got a two-year
advantage.
>> Hey, it seems like the country is just
ready for a [ __ ] let's throw a
[ __ ] clown up there.
>> I know you wanted to bring up the
conspiracy theories first. Being a child
of Epstein and and being locked into the
word conspiracy theories. The term
conspiracy theories is direct evidence
of how [ __ ] up America is to start
with. But in the conspiracy theories,
there's actually somebody showed me a
childhood book from the early 1900s
about Trump becoming president. If that
isn't proof that they have a time
machine, isism, I don't know what is.
>> Yeah, that is weird. That book does
exist and it's [ __ ] weird. It really
does.
>> But you also just said like, am I like a
copy of a copy on a copy of a copy of a
copy? Cuz you just said conspiracy
theorist like 19 [ __ ] times in like a
36 word.
>> No, that's echoes from the bunk acidity
you got from the wrong person.
>> It's actually a 9 in nail.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I stopped I I I eventually
grew past 21 and stopped listening to
'90s depressing suicide music.
>> All right. I can't do the the [ __ ]
Earl thing cuz you bring up '9s suicide
music and um you know, of course
>> that wasn't a claim. Don't don't flag
me.
>> We all know what the '9s were about.
Thank god dope is out of the music
finally,
>> bro. The '9s were about like if you were
my age, you learned what a [ __ ] was
because Bill Clinton got one and they
tried to impeach him over that. And in
hindsight, like
>> tried. Key word. Yeah, they tried.
That's some [ __ ] Dude was just
getting a Hummer on the side.
>> Another interesting side note about
Clinton, least amount of wars for his
pres presidency, most amount of
political assassinations during his
presidency.
>> He didn't get assassinated.
>> No. No. The most amount of political
assassinations occurred under his
presidency. Like Libya and other third
world nations. I'm pretty sure like JFK
and Lincoln got
>> they shot JFK right in front of everyone
for saying he's going to disband their
bank.
>> We all know who's paying for the
country.
>> No, of course Oswald did that [ __ ] Come
on.
>> You believe Oswald did that?
>> Yeah. No,
>> that's that presidential campaign that
win elections right there.
>> I could have made that [ __ ]
>> I would.
>> You can't see straight right now.
>> Fair enough. I work at the
>> Fair enough. Fair enough.
>> You got to stop with those erection
dips, man.
>> Oh, well, no. Well, I'm I'm the test
market. Somebody's got to test them.
>> Although, I do like pretending you're
happy to see me, but I know the truth.
>> I am not.
Like, absolutely.
>> That's just because you don't like
addressing the schizophrenia.
>> Dude, look at me. Obviously, I'm as fun
of as a barrel of monkeys.
>> That's fair. Tell me you're at a party
dancing
>> and look at me. I look like and and you
don't get happier when you see me. You
see me at a nightclub. You're like, "Oh,
my night might have gotten better."
>> That's Yeah, guys. Anybody wearing that
shirt?
>> More fun than a barrel of monkeys.
>> A barrel of monkeys is no fun. You
[ __ ] monkeys are [ __ ]
>> Sorry, I didn't mean to bring up your
abs.
>> You put them in a [ __ ] bar.
>> All right, on that I'm going to We're
going to give it back to Gino. Thanks,
everyone. And we tried.
>> Once again, this is Brady. I am Mystery.
And here again is Cheino. Thank you
everyone.
>> We love all you and I love you, Mister.
>> Brady Mystery, ladies and gentlemen.
Mystery, a good technique for improv is
yes and
>> yes and instead of no not.
>> Jesus. Uh, yeah. Yes. hand. It keeps the
flow going. I love that he crapped on
your musical taste while being a
Grateful Dead fan. How hilarious. How
hilarious. So entitled. You still listen
to high school depressed music? I listen
to this dead guy for 20 years. Whatever.
All right.
I just made all the Grateful D fans in
here so upset. They are seething right
now. There's somebody with a Jerry Berry
tattoo right now who's just like [ __ ]
I knew I hated Chino for a reason. All
right. Uh, we're down to the bottom of
the list. Yes.
>> Yes, you're coming up now. So, it's
doubles night.
>> Does Does anybody want to be Yesh's
partner? Otherwise, he's going to go
solo and I'm going to give him a h half
normal set.
>> Yes. Do you want a partner or do you
want to just do your thing?
>> Oh, you're Kane? Yes.
>> You want to join me and make fun of me?
>> Well, I mean, one of our comics, Shane,
is raising his hand. He's willing to
double with you. You down? All right. We
got double set, ladies and gentlemen,
COMING TO THE STAGE.
Hold on. Hold on. Yes, this is your
first time doing stand up.
>> FRESH MEAT FOR THE GRINDER.
>> First time coming, ladies and gentlemen.
AGAIN FOR SHANE NELSON WITH YES.
>> I'm excited about that Christmas music
to start.
>> Keep singing.
>> I almost missed out on this.
>> What's your name?
>> Yeah, my name's Y. Yeah, I missed out on
the Hobo the the Hobo chauffeur. I
almost didn't come tonight. It's called
the uh the uh uh public transit.
>> And uh so usually usually I'm singing a
a marathon and thing is
>> you're holding this upside down.
>> Oh my god.
>> Oh, it literally can I read this? It l
it literally saysum.
>> So I'm part of a cold.
>> I swear to God. I swear to God it says
that donkey.
>> This is going to be word for word. Let's
go, baby. So, you want to make fun of me
with me?
>> No. No. I'm your best friend. I'm your
partner. I'm your sidekick.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Except during Christmas time. During
Christmas time, it's
at least when I'm walking around here in
Maui. Um, so I wrote down some stuff to
make fun of me and I
>> That's a Home Alone reference.
>> You want to want to read some of this
stuff?
>> Another Home Alone reference.
>> OH, NO.
OH YEAH. I JUST thought I'd come out and
make fun of myself. If anybody wants to
come and help make fun of me,
>> come on up.
>> Friend right here.
>> Me and my friend his name is
>> Oh, I'm I'm Maui's own hobo billionaire.
Yeah. I retired here in 2019. It turned
out that uh anybody who comes here at 28
without a job is a hobo.
>> Um so what about you? Your name is
Shane. Yes, it is. M sure. What's your
name? Oh my gosh.
Except during Christmas. Then when I
walk around Maui, it's
>> Oh, that is Christmas. Whoops. All
right, Shane. Which one's this?
>> Dude, you write backwards.
>> Oh, that's when I first started making a
show. Who wants to be a billionaire?
Turned out that uh going around
hitchhiking like a hobo. Nobody ever
believes a hobo. They have a name here
in Hawaii for a hobo that thinks he's
rich. It's crazy.
>> It mostly says bum bum bum bum bum bum,
but it also says billionaire hobo over
and over again.
>> I swear to God, dude.
>> Show the camera.
>> I'm all of you.
>> This is his diary, so I should ask.
>> Okay.
>> Elsa says, "I'm going to kill myself."
What's that mean?
>> Oh, the time for improv. Oh, right.
>> No, no, no. This isn't improv. So, how
is everybody doing tonight? I'm so
thankful. It's so tough here in Maui.
It's so tough. I know. And it's Asian in
the back. You know,
>> you know it's tough here in Maui and all
that.
>> You know, it's tough here in Maui.
>> It is very tough. Which is a good
premise, dude.
>> Yeah, it's it's super tough here. It is
so tough here that
>> Wait, can I ask the audience A QUESTION?
HOW TOUGH IS IT?
>> So tough.
>> Oh, it's so tough that there is like one
ice cream for every five people here. I
will never forget the day when I opened
one by the local Mana Foods. Oh my gosh,
JUST INSTINCT JUMPED OUT FROM MANA. FAT
PERSON ALL AFTER ME. I barely GOT OUT
ALIVE.
>> BARELY.
>> BARELY. BAR.
WHAT DO YOU WANT? OH MY GOSH. WHAT DO
YOU WANT FROM ME? GIVE ME GIVE ME THAT
ICE CREAM.
>> You're a robot, dude. That sound only
comes from pinning a mic against a
ROBOT'S HEAD. TRUST ME, I KNOW.
>> He's a robot, dude.
>> All right.
>> Yeah. Listen to my sound.
>> Human.
>> Oh,
man. So, me and my 278 wives uh are in
an invisible.
>> Also, humans don't have that many.
>> Tropical island. Guess which one.
>> Which island? Maui.
>> Oh, man. So, tell me some funny things
about you. Cuz I I'm justum bum bum.
Yeah. Funny things about me. I am a hobo
billionaire.
Wow. Does that mean anything to you?
>> I thought I was the only one. I thought
I was the only one. Oh, really? Shade?
Yeah. So, I just thought that I'd come
out here and start making fun of myself
if anybody wants to join me cuz I have a
super serious life. Shane,
>> can you spell your name for us?
>> Yes.
>> Y EJ.
>> What about Shane? Is it S?
>> It's little S, capital H, little A,
little N, little E. Shahane. Shah,
>> which is what makes labeling my
underwear so easy. I buy hands and I
take a Sharpie. I write little S's on my
hands. So everyone know underwear hands.
Sorry. Take it.
>> No. Oh my gosh. Oh my god.
THIS IS SO TERRIFIC. THIS IS so
Okay. All right. We're okay. Okay, I got
my notes.
>> We're back. We're back.
>> Hey, everyone just chill out.
>> Oh my god.
>> Oh, w
the 39th. So, I demand absolute loyalty
with all of my 278 wives.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. It's hard being a polygamist for
me.
>> So, we always have uh openings
>> for wives.
>> Yeah. because I demand absolute loyalty
from
>> Does it has to be a a person who's born
a woman
>> or are you or are you Republican
>> Santa Democrat?
>> I better pick up my garbage. I better
pick up my garbage.
>> All right, let's see what it says.
>> This is what noobs look like, everybody.
Noobs are holding up.
>> He writes an Egyptian.
>> It's mostly pictures of birds.
Hieroglyphics.
>> Oh, no. It's It's something else.
>> Hey, what's up, dude? You're talking.
You're shaved.
>> Do you shave Do you shave your head
every day?
>> I'm Maui's own hobo.
>> And Shane is, too.
>> All right.
>> All right. All right. Okay. We got 10
more minutes.
>> I came here.
>> Buckle up.
>> Am I having a stroke?
>> Whoops. Oh, I I you know I only last the
one out of the 10. Shane, sorry.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> So, I'm an atypical atypical wealthy
guy. Shane,
>> what are you aware?
>> I'm cheap.
>> Okay.
>> I don't pay taxes and I'm
overcompensating for a little.
>> This is YouTube live. I wouldn't mention
the taxes, dude.
>> Oh, man. Uhoh.
>> He pays a bunch of taxes.
>> Oh, boy.
>> All of them.
>> All right. Dig me, Shane. Let's do this,
dude.
>> Okay, let's get started. Let's warm. Oh.
Oh my gosh. All right.
>> All right.
>> It's not Christmas yet. It's not
Christmas.
>> All right. All right. All right. So,
>> this is what it looks like.
>> John, you're having a good time. I like
that.
>> You want us to kiss? All right.
>> No. No. Stand up. Stand up. Stand up.
I'll sit down.
>> No teeth.
I'm all teeth, baby.
>> All right. So, I just want to make fun
of my life. Do you want to make fun?
>> Do we not get the minutes yet?
>> I I don't I don't have anything else to
do. 10 minutes of my life.
>> Longest 10 minutes of my life.
>> Oh my god.
>> If I lasted this long, you have a
question, Jimbo.
>> Shut up.
>> Are we taking questions?
>> We are taking questions. Does anyone
have questions?
>> Anybody questions? Anyone have
questions? Anybody?
>> Anybody else? is moving
>> in paella all the time except during
Christmas.
>> Starter time again.
>> Are you dancing? He's not even dancing,
dude. Jackson, come up here.
That's a hat on more.
>> Long Jasmine. I'm all right.
>> It's not the hat, dude. It's the hat.
>> It's the head.
>> Robot head, dude. Which there's nothing
wrong with robot heads, my brother.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> All right. All right. So, comedy night.
Comedy night's here. Thank you all for
joining us here in Maui. It really is
tough. No doubt.
>> That 8:00 p.m. It's giving me the light.
I
>> appreciate you all. The light. The
light.
>> It is. It's flashing at me.
So, what do you think of the limelight,
Shane?
>> I don't like it. I I regret coming up
here.
>> What do you think about all this money
being a comedian?
>> Well, I regret coming up here.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Also, I I wonder if I CAN GET MY HAT
BACK.
>> This hat is hot, dude.
>> Switch hats again.
>> Oh, wow.
>> And then we're going to switch shirts.
No. Yes. All right.
>> Oh, I got to get better at teamwork
here. Oh, man. Take it away, Shane.
>> Yeah. I'm going to get home and my
girlfriend's going to be like, "How many
hats did you switch with people
tonight?" And that's a lot.
>> Is that a comment or switch hat?
>> Oh.
>> Oh, no. Do you want me to tell her about
you, dude?
>> About me?
>> Yes.
>> No, no, no. I just don't want to tell
you about her.
>> Shut up.
>> We're having everyone ear muffs. Try to
tell her about us or what?
I guess that depends. Do I have to tell
the 278 wives you're coming over?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's logic.
>> No.
>> [ __ ] piss off.
>> No, no, no, no. Stop. Stop.
>> It was nice meeting you. I hope we never
see each other again. Goodbye.
>> Hey, keep it going for that act, huh?
What was that?
What was that? Right. Hey, this might
not be your favorite thing to watch, but
where else are you going to see some
[ __ ] like that, right, guys? Never.
That's like a two That's a That's a
puppet show with real people. [ __ ] the
puppets.
[ __ ] the puppets. We got No, don't. No.
No. [ __ ] the puppets. Do that. Actually,
I'm cool with that's a whole another
show. All right. So, uh, Matthew, where
you at? I don't see you anymore,
Matthew. You still here? Dog man. Got
the dog. Matthew, my buddy Matt, not
here anymore. All right. Uh,
>> Bender, you want to close us out with a
five minute set real quick? Unless or
unless you want me to play with you?
>> I mean, I'll do it. Do you guys want me
to do a second set with this next comic?
>> All right. All right. Cool. We'll close
it out with myself and Bender. Come on
up, Bender. Grab a mic. Mic up, my
friend.
>> All right.
>> I was like, where are you talking from?
>> There you go.
>> Sorry. uh that I came so late. Um I had
to try to rent a moped earlier and for
some reason the guy that was renting
them wasn't available. I don't know.
>> Wait, so you were renting the moped or
renting it out?
>> I was trying to rent one from somebody
but he bailed or something. I don't
know.
>> Trying to rent a moped.
>> One question.
>> Why don't you dream bigger?
>> There's a whole plethora of vehicles to
rent.
>> Uh you can even do like a onehe or a
motorcycle. It can even be in the the
same category. Before we go any further,
we need to set some ground rules.
>> Okay. Sorry. Sorry.
>> Topics that are okay to talk about.
Sure.
>> Okay. So, no racist humor. Got it.
>> Cuz I'm half black. No religious humor
cuz I'm half Jewish.
>> Sure.
>> No humor about people's sexual
orientation cuz
>> Wait, half Jewish? One question. Is that
the same side?
>> Yeah.
>> Right side.
>> Okay. Cuz like the if you're half
Jewish, black, that's like we should
celebrate that. We should talk about
that the entire set. That's please move.
All right.
No, no jokes about um uh sexual
orientation
>> because I'm half gay and no jokes about
uh being uh uh entitled cuz I'm half
care.
>> Okay. Gotcha. Gotcha. So So what does
that leave? Um
>> No, really. You can talk about anything
else.
>> Oh, okay. That's good. That's good. Uh
we we've known each other for quite some
time. We've we've done all types of
events uh with each other. I think this
is the first time we've ever shared a
stage together simultaneously, right?
>> Yes. Right on.
>> I think so.
>> How you feeling?
>> I'm usually I I do audio visual. I'm
usually on that side,
>> not on this side.
>> Sorry. Your Okay. Sorry. Your pattern.
The pattern of your shirt looked like it
was like stitched
>> sweater, right?
>> Yeah. It looked like it was
handstitched, but it's not. That's
>> That's like the teu handstitching. It's
like, well, you know, I was told if you
want to be funny, you have to dress
funny.
>> Well, it looks like the type of pattern
that if I just did this, I could see
your nipple, but it's not.
Unfortunately, I wanted to see some nip,
but it's not happening tonight. Um,
>> right on. So, you are you said you
didn't want to talk about race. Can we
talk about race for a little bit?
>> Why don't we start with religion?
>> Cuz you said you're you're half black.
What's the other half? What What What
else?
>> Black and
>> and Jewish.
>> Okay.
>> Yes. So, want to talk about religion?
>> Cuz that's great. Everyone loves that.
>> We don't have a choice. It seems like
our talk about race is just going to
bring us to religion.
>> Well, so yeah. So last night I was out
and I got in a very interesting
conversation about religion and and one
of the things that that came up is
uh what if one of the religions was
actually the right religion and all the
other religions actually were wrong.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean that
technically that has to be so. Right.
>> Right. And so like you die and you go to
heaven and you're you're a Christian and
and Vishnu is there to greet you and
you're like, "Oh, I've been paying the
wrong bill." [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Who who who would be
the most disappointing religion to find
out they were right.
>> Jehovah's Witness.
>> Jehovah's Witness. Cuz there's only
100,000 people in heaven.
>> Scientology.
>> Scientology. I don't know what they
believe. You go to space and become uh
alien tits. I don't know what they
believe. I don't know what they believe.
I watch South Park. That's what they
said. Uh, who?
>> Scientology.
>> Scientology. That any other more
disappointing religions?
>> Like what if it was some like indigenous
colony that we've just never we like the
one that's like off the coast of Africa?
Like, yeah, we don't talk to them. We're
not allowed to talk to them. Like, well,
they were the right ones. Like, oh [ __ ]
they could have told us. Have you heard
about our Church of Spear?
>> Church of Spear.
Okay. How do you feel about your
religion since you were born into it? Do
you do you Do you love it as as or do
you see
>> Well, I'm I'm not religious and I wasn't
raised religious. It's more of a a
cultural thing.
>> It's more of an entitlement thing.
>> Exactly.
>> Where you're like, "Excuse me, I'm here
to get coffee. I'm also half Jew." And
they're like, "Ah,
>> yes.
>> Gotcha."
>> But it's okay because
>> almond milk cuz we know you can't do
real milk if you're Jewish.
>> I'm Asian. We're the same. We can't do
milk either.
>> So, so I have an Indian friend and uh
And he said to me, you actually if you
go to heaven, you wouldn't see Vishnu.
>> Do you know who you would see?
>> Who?
>> Jesus.
>> Ah. Uh, that's the that's another point
of entitlement.
>> Yes.
>> And and I'm not even Christian, but I
can make fun of other religions.
>> Yeah. I've I've I've often wondered
who's going to greet me at the pearly
gates. You know, you think it's going to
be okay.
>> Wait. You think you're going to go
through the pearly gates?
>> No. No. I think they're going to see me
at the pearly gates and they're going to
tell me go to hell. Like they're gonna
they're gonna pump fake me. They're
gonna be like, "No, Chino, come on here.
You've been a great gay psych." And
they're going to dump me. Uh, for sure.
For sure. But I mean, let's be honest.
Hell has better music,
>> better drugs,
>> better art.
>> Probably better food. I don't know. Most
Christians don't use enough salt. That I
know that for I've eaten enough plates
of free spaghetti to know you guys don't
use salt in your church food. You guys
need to do better. You guys could have
converted me if you used more seasoning.
That's for sure.
>> Instead of putting those American cheese
slices for a high spice.
>> No, no, no, it's not yet, but it could
be. We're We make church food better.
High spice.
>> That's our clientele. Yeah. The power of
price. Make your food hotter than hell.
High spice.
>> Earn the flavor.
>> You got that right.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's That's a good
commercial right there. Um, right on,
man. What? What?
>> Oh, another thing. Please don't leave us
up here for 10 minutes. Don't
>> It's for you. It's for you, man. I'm
just here to support. I'm abroad.
>> This is like my third time doing this.
The first time I thought I was up for 10
minutes and I was up for a minute.
>> Yeah.
>> The second time I was heckled to death,
which I had no [ __ ] comebacks or
anything. And I ended up You left me for
5 minutes instead of three. And I don't
know what happened with our time. I
don't know what's happening this time.
>> Well, it's okay. Every every comedian at
one point in their career tells a joke.
Standup comedy for the first time is
just like having sex and then they throw
in the same three or four punchlines.
It's over too quickly. It all happens so
fast and at the end you just want a
cigarette or whatever their terms are.
So, what would your what would your
punch lines be? Your first time doing
standup comedy is like having sex.
>> Okay.
>> Are you heckling me? No, I'm trying to
set you up. I gave you the setup. Give
me the punch line.
>> Give me the jizz. That's what we want.
>> Yeah. Give me the
>> Give me the jizz.
>> Give me the
>> I got you hard.
>> GIVE HIM THE
>> He just left that, dude. That was the
first time I heard him go.
>> That was all night.
>> All right, we'll take it.
>> So, how do you deal with hecklers,
though?
>> How do you deal with hecklers?
>> Someone heckle.
>> Joe, do do you want honest honest
direction on how to heckle? All right.
>> First thing I do here, I'll give you
guys a little quick little master class.
When I get a heckler, first thing I do
is I identify where they're heckling
from.
>> Did I offend them?
>> Are they trying to offend me or are they
drunk?
>> If I offended them, I pretend like I'm
trying to fix things and then I make
them worse. That's my favorite thing. I
go, "Oh, I'm so sorry I said that. Hey,
let me ask this." And then I double down
and then watch them squirm. If they're
trying to offend me, I try to find uh
the most common thing that I don't like
about them. Like say I'm being heckled
by one of those hot girls in those like
one piece outfits. I'm like I'm not
going to get heckled by somebody who
looks like a trapeze artist or whatever.
Just attack them. And if they're drunk,
then you just [ __ ] point out their
childhood traumas. And that's
>> and that's how you do it, friends. It's
that easy. All right. All right,
>> Ben. You good? Was that
>> That's perfect.
>> Hey, thank you. Give it up for vendor.
Ladies and gentlemen,
>> hope you guys had a good night. Does
anybody else want to get up on stage
tonight? Anybody else want to speak
their mind real quick? Oh, we're we're
at the Anyways, ladies and gentlemen,
get up for pay coffee and bar for
putting this on. What a wonderful
establishment for putting up with us
every Monday. Thank you so much for
braving the potential hurricane. As you
can tell here on Maui, it didn't turn to
much. Let's pray for our brothers in
Niha and Hawaii. Make sure that they're
okay. and get ready for relief efforts
>> because as we know as the neighboring
islands the first thing that we do when
somebody hurt is hurt we help. Get ready
to do that. Uh in the chat I'll share
you information. Uh although some people
in the chat were like it's unfortunate
it didn't hit Maui cuz then these
[ __ ] will get wet. They really don't
like us guys. Uh but hey don't forget to
like and subscribe so we can monetize
your hatred. Uh, nothing would make me
happier,
nothing would make me happier than to
take such a extreme momentum and just
turn it into money into our pockets.
That would be so wonderful. Um, guys,
thank you for joining us. Thank you for
tuning in.
>> Over 50K viewers online. That's kind of
weird, right? Oh. Oh, 66K. Excuse me. I
really short sold that. By the way, we
had like 50 people here tonight at most.
So, that's [ __ ] cool. Thanks for
making this night awesome. Uh, oh,
audience member of the night. Obviously
you two. You guys are my shoe and pick
for audience members of the night. Let
me get you guys some swag real quick.
Um, comedian the night. Uh, it was duo
night. There are none. There are none.
>> The chair and the chair is what the
online wanted. No, I don't have a prize
for comic of the night. So, everybody
did great. Uh, I'm not going to make
anybody stand out more than others. Uh,
next week,
>> should we do characters next week?
>> Character- based comedy. You guys cool
with that? Comedians, you cool with that
next week. Character-based comedy.
>> Doesn't have to be the whole set, just
pull out a little bit of a character.
Uh, dude, we know we know that some
people are going to be just fine. Some
people don't know how to be themselves.
So, that's wonderful. Uh, thank you so
much for joining us, chat. I'll be with
you in a second. Uh, we'll see you next
week. Stay dry. Love you guys. Good
night. BYE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
ATTORNEY,
TOO. Love you.
But yeah,
>> first time
witnesses.
>> Oh no.
Chair, chair, chair, chair, chair,
chair, chair. They love that chair, man.
>> Good to see you,
>> dude.
All right. What's up, chat?
There it is. Your moment of charity as
you ask your cherry awaits
man of cherry man of my word and now
you're an audience of cherry welcome.
Good to see you guys. Thanks for tuning
in. Sorry. Hey, it was a rough one
tonight. I'll be honest with you guys.
Audience, you you know you can tell the
difference between when our shows are
like hitting and when they're and when
they're tough. Tonight was a tough one.
It was a tough one. Thank you for being
here for it, dude. You guys, the ones
who stuck it out the entire one. I'm
impressed. All right, I'm paid to be
here.
I'm glad you guys like the chair. What
we got in comments saying the artist
formerly known as chair?
Am I hosting as Captain Spalding next
week? Every week, baby. That's what I
look like. I'm born like this. Um I
know. Rest in peace, Captain Spalding. I
I guess I'll have to be his uh his
replacement as we get into the remakes.
>> Butt chug some hot sauce.
Some the Sriracha. Oh, the Sriracha is
very butt chugable. Um, out of all the
sauces to butt chug, I think I would
butt chug that one the most. No, sorry.
I think I Thank you, man. Appreciate it.
Got some food here. Oh, what up SDL,
dude? Thanks for coming back again next
week. Appreciate you. You're on a roll.
Thank you. Thank you, Radio Star.
Appreciate it. Uh, I was just doing my
best to make sure the show stayed
entertaining. Uh, doubles are especially
hard. There's a lot of listening
involved and, uh, sometimes comedians
can can get in the tunnel when we're
doing comedy comedy. we just kind of
zone in on what we're trying to say. So,
sometimes you saw that a couple times
tonight, but this is how we learn.
Sometimes a host is going to bring you
back on a show. If you've had a set and
it was great, they want to play with you
on stage. This is a great way to learn
how to do that. Uh, yeah, doubles are
hard. Thank you, some guy. You get it.
Um,
duos did seem kind of difficult. Yeah.
Yeah. It's it's full improv. Uh, people
do try to write for it, but it's really
tough to even prepare for something like
that. So, you need hot sauce for your
eyes after tonight? Diablo, didn't I
send you hot sauce? If I haven't sent
you hot sauce yet, Diablo, message me in
the uh the Comedy Simulator Instagram
and I'll I'll get you some. You deserve
some. Uh get some bomb. Yeah, thank you,
Juan. Appreciate you. We got him some
sauces. Uh appreciate you. Hey, Juan
used to only rip on us and now he That's
one of the nicest things you've said,
Juan Hartman. I appreciate you, brother.
Uh hey, I appreciate you when you're
mean to us, too. I like your comments.
You're one of my favorites. Um, double's
like watching family play Monopoly. Ooh,
Allison nailed it on the head. It is
like watching a a family play Monopoly.
And not like like a real family. Not
like one of those Steepford families,
but like the families that like openly
fight. The ones that like the police
officers of your neighborhood like
recognize you when they come to your
house where they're like, "Hey, buddy.
Everything okay?" What? Just me?
>> All right. You cancelled the trip to
Hawaii thanks to this. Hey, good. We
don't want you.
>> No, you're fine. You're good. What's up?
>> I was just wondering what like the
wholeatic was.
>> Oh, sure. Do you roast?
>> We we do a different theme every week.
So, this this week's theme was double
sets where we had comics doing two sets
or two comics doing a set together. Um,
next week is character comedy. So,
character based stuff
>> or like Yeah. Or like think of uh even
if you're telling a story, maybe just
like be the other person you're talking
about even for a little bit. Uh, it
doesn't have to be your whole set. We
just like I got that.
>> Yeah. We just work in elements to kind
of like stretch out the talent. Okay.
>> Yeah. What's your name, friend?
>> Jordan, man.
>> Jordan. Chino.
>> Good to meet you.
>> Good to meet you. I run this thing every
Monday. We do something different every
week.
>> I run a music venue over at
>> Oh, cool.
>> Yeah. Um,
every year.
>> Hey, let me know. We got some nights
available. We can spread it out.
>> Yeah. Uh, what night?
>> Um, I got Thursdays.
Um, Thursdays is the main open one right
now, but I mean, yeah. our challenge and
sh
>> I get it like we need to like start
catering to
>> other
>> let me know if we can help you out
>> I'll come in I'll come in I'll throw you
>> right on we'll be here every every
Monday so like the lineup for the week
music opening
>> um tomorrow is live band no sorry
Thursday um tomorrow's bingo Wednesday's
trivia Thursday is live band karaoke
Friday and Saturday are house DJ
Yeah. Yeah. What was your name?
>> Chino.
>> Do this one more time.
>> Jordan.
>> Jordan. Right on, brother. Good to meet
you.
>> Hell yeah. Sorry. Just talking about
more shows booking. We're going to be
ordering more. Just got to keep it
spicy. Hey, appreciate you. Uh, Juan,
don't forget, use the code com 10. You
get 10% off your order. Uh, Manson
Family. Yeah, that's Yeah, right. Manson
family playing Monopoly 100%. I swear
the Dora the Explorer girl is lowkey
great at duos. Yeah. You know, she Sasha
brought a great energy tonight with
Craig cuz Craig like Craig can be a
little like overwhelming like he wants
to like he wants to take s he wants to
use his words a lot. Sasha did a great
job of just like kind of verbal judoing
him and redirecting them. I think we
really got to see some flashes of why
she wants to do comedy. That's what I
love uh seeing the weeklies and
sometimes you see some new comics come
and you're like I don't know why they're
like interested in comedy. Maybe they
don't seem naturally funny off the bat,
but every once in a while you'll see
little flashes and you're like, "Oh,
that's the comedian inside." That's why
I've been doing comedy for so long.
That's why I've been cultivating comedy
for so long, cuz I live for those
moments of seeing just that little flash
of comedy in them. It's wonderful. Uh
yeah, catch you on the next one.
Appreciate you. Where do we sell the hot
sauce? Uh very easy. It's on
highspice.com. That's hpspice.com.
Uh it brings up our website in the promo
area. Type in com10 to get 10% off.
>> And also say hi to Mr. Shane. Shane
Nelson.
>> Hello.
>> Probably comic of the night. I don't
know.
>> Me and him were the only two that did it
twice. So I guess it's us
>> twice. We came. We conquered.
>> He came again.
>> Yeah. Good job, Shane. Appreciate Shane.
Shane. That was Shane, not Jackson, by
the way. That was Shane. Um, it's like,
you know, sometimes you got to write the
the first letter of your twin's name on
their head to know which one it is. Hey,
there's your moderator, Jimbo. Say hi to
Jimbo.
>> Or you get put in timeout.
>> Your moderator who doesn't moderate it.
>> I don't like that it makes me put them
in timeout. It's so weird.
>> He literally just reads your comments
and make sure you're not saying any like
horrible words.
>> Like and comment if you think we should
start busting open sports card packs at
the end of the night.
>> Sasha and and Yeshu show. That That
could be fun. I'd I'd listen to that
podcast for sure.
>> What are you saying about me? Be nice to
me.
>> Jimbo,
>> they know the rules. They know the
rules. I said I have the power. I don't
deserve the power, but I have it.
>> Leonard Scannard.
>> Hey, thank you guys. Appreciate you.
Hey, w chat.
>> Why do they like you?
>> I don't know. I don't know. It's the
only people I know.
>> You don't know him.
>> You don't know me.
>> We like each other.
>> I don't know them either. That's why I
like them.
>> But we do on a level. I mean,
>> I feel like I know a lot of our
commenters just based on your senses of
humor. Yeah,
>> like after seeing literally hundreds of
your comments, some of you have been
putting in so much information, I feel
like I'm like an AI data center
>> where I'm like, "Oh, now I can write
just like you." Nuhuh. I I appreciate
your guys' humor. Even the ones that are
mean to us, like I could tell you're
being funny. It's hilarious.
>> Said Jimmo looks heavier than last week.
Yeah, my pockets full.
>> Why is it heavier? You should get that
checked out.
>> I don't know. At this age, they're not
supposed to be getting bigger unless
it's a tuma.
>> My coin purse. This is not the tulum.
>> Oh, we're doing duos right now.
>> Yeah, right. My penis didn't get bigger.
>> That was um That was definitely a fever
dream. How'd you feel? I thought it was
awesome, though.
>> No, tonight was rough. That was tough.
>> So, okay. I Duos is tough. Duos is
[ __ ] hard. It's a hard comedy muscle
to scratch. Um and just like All right.
My John set, right? I thought it was
hilarious, but it's a bit It's very
tough as a comic to like not think it's
personal or like not think about what
everyone else is thinking about the set,
but you just got to riff off each other.
Yeah. And you got to make decisions and
you got to kind of stick to them. Uh it
was really interesting to see uh M Mr. E
really made a strong decision in being
kind of anti, but it also didn't really
help the set move forward a little bit,
>> right? It was staging on that.
>> So that's why uh improv has has certain
techniques to keep the scene going. It's
not cheating. It's not like the trick to
improv. It just kind of makes sure the
scene keeps moving. Add information.
Yes. And instead of denying, uh having
emotional reactions, changing stage
pictures, establishing relationship.
These are all things that you can do to
make a scene move forward. Uh that's
that's just a good example of seeing
denials and where they kind of become
book.
>> Yes. And the Jews did 911.
>> Is that
>> And if you can't say anything to that,
just have an emotional reaction.
>> Did I do that right?
>> There you go. Um yeah, so we're we're
demonetized before we're monetized. Uh
we always have we always have to thank
for that. How did the show? Uh yeah,
Jimbo did a show last week uh for being
comic of the night. I heard he did
great.
>> Yeah. Uh Jose Raymond. It was super
funny. Tell us about the show. Uh it was
it was awesome, man. It was sold out. It
was about 150 some people, 120, 150
people. Fully packed. Uh I learned so
much from Jose Raymond doing an hour up
there. That was wild to watch him do an
hour. But I thought I slayed. I did 5
minutes. I did pretty good stuff. Um I
know you guys, this is open mic. Most of
the time we're working on stuff here.
This is us us working out terrible jokes
that we know are terrible. We're just
trying to work them out. Um, you guys
should subscribe to everybody so when
they post their actual content.
>> Most of us, for most of us, this is an
open mic. For some of us, this is all
that we have.
>> This is true. This is true.
>> Not myself and Jimbo. We We have some
things going on, but for some people,
this is the only comedy they do.
>> Look, if you're a weirdo and you want to
get weird in virtual reality with me and
Chino, hit us up. Every so often, we'll
pop on some VR.
>> Yeah. This Thursday, uh, check me out
with Fa to Render, and we're giving away
hot sauce there, too. Yeah. Hey, pop in,
friends. Check out the channel. Eddie
and Aaron from the double set earlier.
>> Aaron all the way from from LA. From LA.
Yeah. Look out.
>> Yeah. Uh what what what's the show that
you run again called?
>> Uh the dead pants show and the last
comic dancing.
>> Dead show. You're going to be doing a
comedy store, right? Coming up.
>> I'm doing the Rose Battle. The Comedy
Star.
>> Oh, you're doing the Rose Battle.
>> Yes. Get up for the Rose Battle.
>> I won the last one. So, we'll see.
>> Congratulations. Keep that record roll
in.
>> It's fun to be back. It's great. Love
this concert. Tell our viewers where
they can find you on social media.
>> Yeah, so it's Aaron E R Y N um Guy Vet.
So G Y V E T T E
>> like Corvette, but I'm a war vet with
guys.
>> A guy vet.
>> Guy vet. Yeah, exactly.
>> Dude, killer. Thanks for Thanks for
coming back to our mic.
>> Yes.
>> Great to see you. How How long you want
to live for?
>> Just a few days.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> I'll try miss some days open. See if we
can we can hang out. Good to see you.
Come on.
>> Hell yeah.
>> Massage this big piece of me. Oh, I am a
piece of masses piece of meat tenderiz.
>> If you want if you want Davidson
mouth, you know where to go.
Highspice.com.
>> Lynn Davidson, if you got a lot of
jokes, come on down to the the comedy
show every Monday night. Check us out.
If you can come to Maui, we'll give you
stage time. We'll treat you like uh
royalty. Um we love you. Uh right on,
guys. I mean, unless there's anything
else you want to say, I think we've I
think we've uh harmed you enough for an
evening. No, thanks for tuning in. Uh
Doubles night was rough. I'll be honest
with you. I'll level with you. Tonight
was probably a rough show for you guys
to watch. I'm sorry. Thank you for
sticking around. Uh you guys truly have
a deep sense of humor if you made it all
the way this way to the end. Uh nobody
signed the waiver to pair with Dumpster
Danny. We missed Dumpster Danny tonight.
He wasn't here. I would have loved to
have had him on the show. I would have
loved to have done doubles with him. He
does something weird to my head. So, I
would love to do that. Uh, here you go.
So, I'd make Jimbo die laughing. Um,
yes, that would be what he would prefer
cuz he talks about how much he would
like to die so often. You got joke for
me, Harley Quinn. I appreciate it. I can
only imagine what it could possibly be.
Um,
>> oh, but you're handicapped and you lived
in North Carolina. Huh. I'm trying to
think of how we can get around that. Um,
you know, I might be going out to North
Carolina pretty soon for some shows. If
there's any way we can make something
happen, maybe we can, then let's stay in
contact. Uh, that that's not for a
while, though. So, just keep watching
the show. We'll figure out. We'll see
you guys next week. Uh, hopefully the
drinks were doubles, too. Good one,
radio. That is that is the hope. Um, we
have a new bartender in tonight, so I
think she was pretty heavy with the
pour. Um, yes. Yes, Candy Jack, you did
miss most of the show. But don't worry,
this happens every Monday, 7:15 Hawaii
time, wherever that is. If you're
Pacific, that's 10 o'clock. East Coast,
that's like 2 o'clock uh or midnight or
something like that. I don't know. My
math is bad. I'm a M high graduate. Good
night, chat. Appreciate you. Good night,
guys. Good night.
>> Does not get his flowers enough. CHINO'S
THE [ __ ] MAN.
>> Appreciate you guys. Hey, thanks. Thanks
for just being here. We love you. We
appreciate you. We'll see you next week.
Aloha. Goodbye.